TAGTUPLE 3 δ I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 24 Browning I-PER
TAGTUPLE 15 convoy O
TAGTUPLE 20 Express I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Sutherland I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Malory I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 25 minerals O
TAGTUPLE 3 Act I-PER
TAGTUPLE 19 hang O
TAGTUPLE 114 let O
TAGTUPLE 468 n't O
TAGTUPLE 1 Engineering I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 67 updated O
TAGTUPLE 1 Leinster I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 <Xx-Xdx> I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 W. I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 14 raced O
TAGTUPLE 77 La I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 <\> O
TAGTUPLE 4 Boxer I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 ten I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 department I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 TNT I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 4 republic I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 43 Stirner I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Bromley I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 Historian I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 11 nerves O
TAGTUPLE 148 Federal I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 10 Venice I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 IHF I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 Bad I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 41 Korean I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 11 occurrences O
TAGTUPLE 1 Inland I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 intermittent O
TAGTUPLE 2 James I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 Gomera I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 17 intensely O
TAGTUPLE 5 Nashville I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Deccan I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 17 intervening O
TAGTUPLE 29 SPD I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 sulfur O
TAGTUPLE 16 u O
TAGTUPLE 57 restaurants O
TAGTUPLE 17 wetlands O
TAGTUPLE 3 Sue I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 48 discontinued O
TAGTUPLE 16 Triangle I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 26 advocacy O
TAGTUPLE 13 LGPL I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Doctor I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Ed O
TAGTUPLE 12 Soddy I-PER
TAGTUPLE 16 Rainbow I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Son I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 105 determine O
TAGTUPLE 8 al. O
TAGTUPLE 2 Batman O
TAGTUPLE 4 800 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 C. I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 40 structured O
TAGTUPLE 14 Al I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Bulgaria O
TAGTUPLE 20 accusative O
TAGTUPLE 8 soda O
TAGTUPLE 1 Bern I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 15 IX I-PER
TAGTUPLE 10 Pannonia I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 4 Too O
TAGTUPLE 17 <XXXxx> I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 20 penned O
TAGTUPLE 2 Chan I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 home I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 Coventry I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 8 Motown I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 119 indeed O
TAGTUPLE 2 Automobile I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 32 FORTRAN I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 Hart I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 26 fielder O
TAGTUPLE 1 clashes I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 448 uses O
TAGTUPLE 9 scan O
TAGTUPLE 7 boyhood O
TAGTUPLE 156 Napoleon I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 ascendancy O
TAGTUPLE 12 pouring O
TAGTUPLE 7 Nance I-PER
TAGTUPLE 20 rebranded O
TAGTUPLE 9 Nothing O
TAGTUPLE 7 contemporaneous O
TAGTUPLE 50 1849 O
TAGTUPLE 5 707 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 pods O
TAGTUPLE 3 Passy I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 nun O
TAGTUPLE 69 phenomena O
TAGTUPLE 11 Federated I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 3 Hard I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 librarians O
TAGTUPLE 12 resolver O
TAGTUPLE 4 Schaefer I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Dock I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 Flashback I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 Organization I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Baku O
TAGTUPLE 5 slick O
TAGTUPLE 8 gilded O
TAGTUPLE 15 flour O
TAGTUPLE 8 ELDR I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Elbing I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 racing I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 Ole I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 44 thrown O
TAGTUPLE 12 spreadsheet O
TAGTUPLE 15 Austin I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 30 trades O
TAGTUPLE 5 Jérôme I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Vanity I-PER
TAGTUPLE 60 Norse I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 9 bandy O
TAGTUPLE 1 DIN I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 jars O
TAGTUPLE 15 1512 O
TAGTUPLE 10 Wendy I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 demoted O
TAGTUPLE 72 atoms O
TAGTUPLE 16 discovers O
TAGTUPLE 355 20th O
TAGTUPLE 8 They I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 77 Red I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 EDGE O
TAGTUPLE 92 Technology I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Barr I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 balancing O
TAGTUPLE 36 contents O
TAGTUPLE 39 treasure O
TAGTUPLE 6 retractable O
TAGTUPLE 269 28 O
TAGTUPLE 302 below O
TAGTUPLE 24 Assembly I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 26 Aston I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 22 foreigners O
TAGTUPLE 7 stricken O
TAGTUPLE 13 pray O
TAGTUPLE 4 All-America I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 3 fandom I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 interpretations I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 14 Second I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 stumbled O
TAGTUPLE 6 knighthood O
TAGTUPLE 21 disposal O
TAGTUPLE 10 Kiss I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 8 reelection O
TAGTUPLE 11 Industries I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 three-letter O
TAGTUPLE 18 converting O
TAGTUPLE 80 publisher O
TAGTUPLE 4 Bronx I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 159 distribution O
TAGTUPLE 34 Opera I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 dear O
TAGTUPLE 5 singularity O
TAGTUPLE 3 Shirley I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 16 DKW I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 20 <X..X.> I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 11 downhill O
TAGTUPLE 6 Verde I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 620 months O
TAGTUPLE 1 Pitch I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 4 Tatars I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 10 yacht O
TAGTUPLE 14 translator O
TAGTUPLE 1 archbishopric I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 30 Age I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 19 Depending O
TAGTUPLE 38 embraced O
TAGTUPLE 13 1.9 O
TAGTUPLE 65 genres O
TAGTUPLE 292 write O
TAGTUPLE 1 17 I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 Karnataka I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Republika I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 121 16th O
TAGTUPLE 322 fall O
TAGTUPLE 52 plateau O
TAGTUPLE 25 MVP O
TAGTUPLE 5 Advisor O
TAGTUPLE 7 OPS O
TAGTUPLE 1 u I-PER
TAGTUPLE 3 Curtiss I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 denominator O
TAGTUPLE 27 1829 O
TAGTUPLE 54 electronics O
TAGTUPLE 17 chronicler O
TAGTUPLE 38 troubles O
TAGTUPLE 53 160 O
TAGTUPLE 9 Horse I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 122 corporate O
TAGTUPLE 94 categories O
TAGTUPLE 9 tripled O
TAGTUPLE 13 extraordinarily O
TAGTUPLE 34 sparked O
TAGTUPLE 1 Scrolls I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Duran I-PER
TAGTUPLE 31 Crystal I-PER
TAGTUPLE 153 followers O
TAGTUPLE 2 union I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 nationalisation O
TAGTUPLE 6 junk O
TAGTUPLE 5 glyph O
TAGTUPLE 1 Falls I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 newspapers I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 LANTIRN I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 tetrameter O
TAGTUPLE 12 overly O
TAGTUPLE 24 caps O
TAGTUPLE 2 Prison I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 21 vastly O
TAGTUPLE 5 Cannon I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 Northern O
TAGTUPLE 8 Its I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 modified I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 50 quantities O
TAGTUPLE 67 roll O
TAGTUPLE 1 Jones I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 rockets I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Liddell I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Tolman I-PER
TAGTUPLE 17 teens O
TAGTUPLE 3 Nast I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 3 Marriage O
TAGTUPLE 5 Halton I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 Ackroyd I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 Renowned O
TAGTUPLE 2 creation I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 13 Federico I-PER
TAGTUPLE 9 Loeb I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 December I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 12 Sumter I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 8 Herbie I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 Loretta I-PER
TAGTUPLE 67 Lugosi I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Sacrifice O
TAGTUPLE 4 Sunny I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 12 reissued O
TAGTUPLE 4 African I-PER
TAGTUPLE 137 implemented O
TAGTUPLE 142 distinction O
TAGTUPLE 1558 because O
TAGTUPLE 1 Match I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 61 relating O
TAGTUPLE 124 fixed O
TAGTUPLE 13 Freeman I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Mariners I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Constantinople I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 681 market O
TAGTUPLE 1 Internationale I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 4 Zhou I-PER
TAGTUPLE 426 Its O
TAGTUPLE 1 Arlington I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 8 eloquent O
TAGTUPLE 38 emissions O
TAGTUPLE 1 Redskins I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Facing I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 expansion I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 Bolton I-PER
TAGTUPLE 20 sizable O
TAGTUPLE 2 disengagement I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 9 playback O
TAGTUPLE 11 obsessed O
TAGTUPLE 6 hardliners O
TAGTUPLE 26 Janeiro I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 leadership I-PER
TAGTUPLE 19 consult O
TAGTUPLE 2 Mozilla I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Isabel I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 3 Dan I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Upon I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 3 <dXxx> I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 99 priests O
TAGTUPLE 1 That I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 brand I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 15 phases O
TAGTUPLE 17 Norman I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 194 houses O
TAGTUPLE 10 Fair I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 46 fortified O
TAGTUPLE 33 Tolkien I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 Novella I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Frédéric I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 mid-70s O
TAGTUPLE 1 Journey I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 <~/.xx> O
TAGTUPLE 12 Rouge I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Guangzhou I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Torino I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 17 defected O
TAGTUPLE 6 aground O
TAGTUPLE 4 Cal I-PER
TAGTUPLE 16 Utrecht I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 paste O
TAGTUPLE 25 mistress O
TAGTUPLE 1 Silent I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 15 taller O
TAGTUPLE 17 implicated O
TAGTUPLE 3 Devi I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Anyone O
TAGTUPLE 36 Unfortunately O
TAGTUPLE 11 undersea O
TAGTUPLE 9 Theodora I-PER
TAGTUPLE 10 Religious O
TAGTUPLE 2 Kirk I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 TX-0 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 quarrying O
TAGTUPLE 82 servers O
TAGTUPLE 32 subtle O
TAGTUPLE 130 Meanwhile O
TAGTUPLE 11 Online I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 13 locomotive O
TAGTUPLE 15 Memorial I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Halifax I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 12 alleging O
TAGTUPLE 6 debugging O
TAGTUPLE 1 Deer I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 mediums O
TAGTUPLE 5 Steinitz I-PER
TAGTUPLE 3 Apostles I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 12 Frances I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 video I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 11 lagoons O
TAGTUPLE 1 Flag I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Prison I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 16 same-sex O
TAGTUPLE 5 anointing O
TAGTUPLE 2 Son O
TAGTUPLE 12 28,000 O
TAGTUPLE 1 Me I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2128 several O
TAGTUPLE 10 lure O
TAGTUPLE 14 iTunes I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 thank O
TAGTUPLE 6 pillow O
TAGTUPLE 12 Cities I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 13 grapes O
TAGTUPLE 43 Law I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 3 departure I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 3 Travel I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 Iphitus I-PER
TAGTUPLE 83 victories O
TAGTUPLE 84 rain O
TAGTUPLE 5 revising O
TAGTUPLE 5 Fréchet I-PER
TAGTUPLE 79 crash O
TAGTUPLE 93 varying O
TAGTUPLE 2 Note I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 Bob I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 al-Mansur I-PER
TAGTUPLE 12 Negro I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 9 ventured O
TAGTUPLE 1 Avengers I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 7 interviewer O
TAGTUPLE 2 <dxXxx> I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Mythos I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 3 I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Kong I-PER
TAGTUPLE 4 Piers I-PER
TAGTUPLE 10 crashing O
TAGTUPLE 430 Russia I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 3 Grampian I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 Graphics I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Morse O
TAGTUPLE 4 Torn I-PER
TAGTUPLE 14 asset O
TAGTUPLE 12 Average O
TAGTUPLE 10 ushered O
TAGTUPLE 5 NIBRS I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 23 rainy O
TAGTUPLE 6 Southwold I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 12 perspectives O
TAGTUPLE 31 migrated O
TAGTUPLE 6 precluded O
TAGTUPLE 22 undergone O
TAGTUPLE 7 alerted O
TAGTUPLE 12 embryo O
TAGTUPLE 16 sells O
TAGTUPLE 15 commencement O
TAGTUPLE 5 cross-section O
TAGTUPLE 8 628 O
TAGTUPLE 5 irreverent O
TAGTUPLE 9 Hollerith I-PER
TAGTUPLE 3 museum I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 12 Unable O
TAGTUPLE 10 Rijndael I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 rationalist O
TAGTUPLE 7 Sheedy I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 battles I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 volunteers I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 Konerko I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 a I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Cardozo I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 40 Gettysburg I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 9 investigative O
TAGTUPLE 28 emotion O
TAGTUPLE 2332 part O
TAGTUPLE 1 Clapton I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 Butler I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 24 <Xxx.> I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 54 boom O
TAGTUPLE 371 intended O
TAGTUPLE 10 POP I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Quatre I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 Lamentations I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Pavlov I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 12 disposition O
TAGTUPLE 25 Casey I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 connotes O
TAGTUPLE 1 Perry I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Frank I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 multi-billion O
TAGTUPLE 2 Goddess I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 Atacama I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 1951 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 privatised O
TAGTUPLE 5 Spellbound I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 150 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Technical O
TAGTUPLE 28 resembling O
TAGTUPLE 1 seizing I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 341 hand O
TAGTUPLE 2 Orpheus I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 10 Veterans I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 44 paternal O
TAGTUPLE 91 dialect O
TAGTUPLE 1 Manastır I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 supermarket O
TAGTUPLE 11 1694 O
TAGTUPLE 12 Rules I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 12 craters O
TAGTUPLE 3 2020 I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 109 convention O
TAGTUPLE 11 Base I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 Poland I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 8 stakes O
TAGTUPLE 48 Law I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Mint I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 Data I-PER
TAGTUPLE 19 charging O
TAGTUPLE 18 bounds O
TAGTUPLE 12 preach O
TAGTUPLE 386 society O
TAGTUPLE 11 genuinely O
TAGTUPLE 2 Row I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 69 innovations O
TAGTUPLE 21 millimeters O
TAGTUPLE 1 <XX.xx> I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 Millikan I-PER
TAGTUPLE 32 pseudonym O
TAGTUPLE 8 Domenico I-PER
TAGTUPLE 28 bench O
TAGTUPLE 7 eroding O
TAGTUPLE 6 replays O
TAGTUPLE 7 Santer I-PER
TAGTUPLE 86 terminal O
TAGTUPLE 5 Burgundy I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Ricardo I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Anton I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 7 Deutschland I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 10 antimony O
TAGTUPLE 2 BASE I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 12 Pamphilus I-PER
TAGTUPLE 14 distributing O
TAGTUPLE 67 doctor O
TAGTUPLE 15 clinic O
TAGTUPLE 5 Hibernian I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 15 innate O
TAGTUPLE 41 programming I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Police I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 4 post-Soviet I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Petersen I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 3 Manager I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 eastern I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 neutrality I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 20 IAU I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 17 Our I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 21 Balderus I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Philosophical O
TAGTUPLE 3 <:x.dd> O
TAGTUPLE 6 novellas O
TAGTUPLE 12 substitution O
TAGTUPLE 1 Right I-PER
TAGTUPLE 122 emphasis O
TAGTUPLE 5 1582 O
TAGTUPLE 1 O'Donnell I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 prerequisite O
TAGTUPLE 95 threatened O
TAGTUPLE 6 roleplaying O
TAGTUPLE 3 Venter I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 63 expense O
TAGTUPLE 14 flop O
TAGTUPLE 88 Cheers I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 Wolff I-PER
TAGTUPLE 9 Bagwell I-PER
TAGTUPLE 12 manually O
TAGTUPLE 7 saxophone O
TAGTUPLE 34 Basque I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 Falkland I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 113 graphics O
TAGTUPLE 9 Xerox I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 12 Saxo I-PER
TAGTUPLE 28 Beach I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 8 Scheele I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 G2 I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 3 <Xx/Xxx> I-PER
TAGTUPLE 184 Due O
TAGTUPLE 24 jewelry O
TAGTUPLE 217 resulting O
TAGTUPLE 6 vampires O
TAGTUPLE 97 educated O
TAGTUPLE 27 Río I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 Gang I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 18 succumbed O
TAGTUPLE 53 cruisers O
TAGTUPLE 5 na I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 Lewes I-PER
TAGTUPLE 30 co-operation O
TAGTUPLE 3 None I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 91 Chaucer I-PER
TAGTUPLE 12 Radical I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 105 Commodore I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 flag I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 direct I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 37 pennant O
TAGTUPLE 2 Moravia I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 9 nurtured O
TAGTUPLE 23 Kaltenbrunner I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 bleachers O
TAGTUPLE 92 Bede I-PER
TAGTUPLE 15 moratorium O
TAGTUPLE 2 Moravian I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 42 tours O
TAGTUPLE 14 Aberdeen I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 7 cameos O
TAGTUPLE 8 10.1 O
TAGTUPLE 8 shook O
TAGTUPLE 2 conquest I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 25 galaxy O
TAGTUPLE 6 SOS I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 Loma I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 24 characterised O
TAGTUPLE 77 daughters O
TAGTUPLE 6 geologists O
TAGTUPLE 10 clinched O
TAGTUPLE 8 penetrate O
TAGTUPLE 1 1992 I-PER
TAGTUPLE 208 visit O
TAGTUPLE 8 ice I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 4 Fighter I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 7 script I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 B.C. I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 18 alienation O
TAGTUPLE 6 consume O
TAGTUPLE 1264 At O
TAGTUPLE 9 Long O
TAGTUPLE 6 leverage O
TAGTUPLE 8 Facing O
TAGTUPLE 9 PHP I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Payne I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 11 1024 O
TAGTUPLE 60 uprising O
TAGTUPLE 14 Kiss I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 103 accident O
TAGTUPLE 6 Branch I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 28 reacted O
TAGTUPLE 77 Barks I-PER
TAGTUPLE 16 Sox I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 Skaro I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Francia I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 Michigan I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 65 assembled O
TAGTUPLE 16 promulgated O
TAGTUPLE 5 Potsdam I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 41 prophecy O
TAGTUPLE 10 4.2 O
TAGTUPLE 8 1675 O
TAGTUPLE 24 supervised O
TAGTUPLE 1 Gertrude I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 43 Lanka I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 21 begged O
TAGTUPLE 9576 had O
TAGTUPLE 55 Soviet I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 66 Sicily I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 81 psychological O
TAGTUPLE 1 fires I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 Baez I-PER
TAGTUPLE 11 Trench I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 Films I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 welcomes O
TAGTUPLE 16 James I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 69 Song I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Immigration I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 Rochelle I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 4 IRC O
TAGTUPLE 5 enthused O
TAGTUPLE 4 comics I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 Concord I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 8 Northampton I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 Laurier I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 Ordnance I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 8 590 O
TAGTUPLE 3 agreement I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 10 charted O
TAGTUPLE 62 ITV I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 11 Curtain I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 22 rejoined O
TAGTUPLE 28 Antigua I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 90 1896 O
TAGTUPLE 7 nightclubs O
TAGTUPLE 23 whites O
TAGTUPLE 16 18,000 O
TAGTUPLE 9 Yamuna I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Heat I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 13 classroom O
TAGTUPLE 44 hospitals O
TAGTUPLE 8 Valens I-PER
TAGTUPLE 9 Island I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 22 Mosque I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Chaldeans I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 cheering O
TAGTUPLE 182 Department I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 NATO I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 Darling I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 316 remain O
TAGTUPLE 10 enforcing O
TAGTUPLE 18 1948 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 44 dominate O
TAGTUPLE 2 Kauffman I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 21 Eyes I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 12 Tbilisi I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 93 Alliance I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 29 Keillor I-PER
TAGTUPLE 22 truths O
TAGTUPLE 3 Silas I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 banners O
TAGTUPLE 8 Languedoc I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 baton O
TAGTUPLE 31 comprised O
TAGTUPLE 39 commemorate O
TAGTUPLE 4 Opium I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 jet I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 93 On I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 11 jam O
TAGTUPLE 2 against I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 OSI I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 13 Spectrum I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 22984 by O
TAGTUPLE 1 Debussy I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 turnovers O
TAGTUPLE 7 intimidated O
TAGTUPLE 9 N.D. I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 UNIVAC I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 17 clerk O
TAGTUPLE 1 toolkit I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 13 Notwithstanding O
TAGTUPLE 99 amounts O
TAGTUPLE 15 .500 O
TAGTUPLE 5 nullified O
TAGTUPLE 1 <xX.xx> I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 13 Taraki I-PER
TAGTUPLE 98 seriously O
TAGTUPLE 6 Broughton I-PER
TAGTUPLE 33 missionaries O
TAGTUPLE 1 Catwoman O
TAGTUPLE 30 Lineker I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 Ariel I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 troubling O
TAGTUPLE 1 littoral I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 rhetorically O
TAGTUPLE 1 Monitor I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 3 Montpellier I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 38 metropolitan I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 66 Gotham I-PER
TAGTUPLE 89 Artemis I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 Protests O
TAGTUPLE 21 backwards O
TAGTUPLE 2 Jihad I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Speer I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 16 marijuana O
TAGTUPLE 9 Mari I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Marlborough I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 Pelopidas I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Moran I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Hundred I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 12 potent O
TAGTUPLE 34 loan O
TAGTUPLE 12 Webster I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 Lucille I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 Airlines I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 17 Suiko I-PER
TAGTUPLE 310 done O
TAGTUPLE 2 Byron I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Twenty I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 quitting O
TAGTUPLE 147 technique O
TAGTUPLE 1 Kursk I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 41 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 32 fencing O
TAGTUPLE 2 ethics I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 363 Japan I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 11 intrigue O
TAGTUPLE 9 Jerzy I-PER
TAGTUPLE 28 Rabbi O
TAGTUPLE 16 Library I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Resistance I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 Pikes I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 10 renovations O
TAGTUPLE 59 Nintendo I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 8 axes O
TAGTUPLE 5 Demographics I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 du O
TAGTUPLE 45 ISO I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 33 1812 O
TAGTUPLE 7 onslaught O
TAGTUPLE 6 Somerville I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 10 tier O
TAGTUPLE 5 infallible O
TAGTUPLE 1 al-Qaeda I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 54 drummer O
TAGTUPLE 94 Eastern I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 111 <X.X.> I-PER
TAGTUPLE 242 alternative O
TAGTUPLE 48 anarchists O
TAGTUPLE 37 Father O
TAGTUPLE 2 Lenin I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 151 O
TAGTUPLE 7 deprogramming O
TAGTUPLE 114 visitors O
TAGTUPLE 32 exploitation O
TAGTUPLE 100 White I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 3 Bugatti I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 corpus I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 Kaufmann I-PER
TAGTUPLE 3 Prime I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 341 O
TAGTUPLE 5 Jean-Michel I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 murder I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 <Xx-.xx> I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 82 Jordan I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 32 Prayer I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 19 mainframe O
TAGTUPLE 34 verbal O
TAGTUPLE 7 Maritsa I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 54 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 19 landlocked O
TAGTUPLE 574 sent O
TAGTUPLE 209 nor O
TAGTUPLE 6 1744 O
TAGTUPLE 10 Mercedes I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 715 Party I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 42 beaten O
TAGTUPLE 147 rapid O
TAGTUPLE 166 core O
TAGTUPLE 1 Gaynor I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 Oz I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 wandered O
TAGTUPLE 1 U.S O
TAGTUPLE 8 Helsingør I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 22 3.0 O
TAGTUPLE 5 Bosschaert I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Charcot O
TAGTUPLE 10 Vivendi I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 58 steady O
TAGTUPLE 18 merit O
TAGTUPLE 167 sets O
TAGTUPLE 34 Rousseau I-PER
TAGTUPLE 12 Complex I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 79 beings O
TAGTUPLE 363 taking O
TAGTUPLE 19 retailers O
TAGTUPLE 28 Nation I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 <Xx-.Xxx> I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 Geyser I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 2200 O
TAGTUPLE 48 governance O
TAGTUPLE 1 Wolf O
TAGTUPLE 6 Thursday I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 10 Huelva I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 58 synthesis O
TAGTUPLE 3 Carcassonne I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 67 prize O
TAGTUPLE 14 Russia I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 Goodyear I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 13 Seydlitz I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 14 NDP I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 pastures O
TAGTUPLE 12 emperor I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 refinements O
TAGTUPLE 7 HK I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 3 fall I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 concert I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 23 Virginia I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 257 daughter O
TAGTUPLE 5 distrustful O
TAGTUPLE 27 shortages O
TAGTUPLE 402 player O
TAGTUPLE 6 Tetris I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 52 Massoud I-PER
TAGTUPLE 25 combines O
TAGTUPLE 7 downplayed O
TAGTUPLE 6 enchanted O
TAGTUPLE 52 Day I-PER
TAGTUPLE 10 turnout O
TAGTUPLE 1 Quinn I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 10 Tunis I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 Henry I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 106 Soon O
TAGTUPLE 26 George I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 44 chiefly O
TAGTUPLE 2 Bundaberg I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 McCartney I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Gerontius I-PER
TAGTUPLE 17 Joshua I-PER
TAGTUPLE 4 Theft I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 522 <Xx-Xxx> I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 cruelty O
TAGTUPLE 11 Torbay I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 8 wheeled O
TAGTUPLE 2 Switzerland I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 70 Cayman I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 13 couscous O
TAGTUPLE 6 shadowed O
TAGTUPLE 1 Kremlin I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Azeri I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 8 tails O
TAGTUPLE 5 coexist O
TAGTUPLE 264 share O
TAGTUPLE 430 I I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Freemason I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 Bukhara I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 growers O
TAGTUPLE 1 Marine O
TAGTUPLE 9 blended O
TAGTUPLE 22 Tourism O
TAGTUPLE 24 simulation O
TAGTUPLE 6 Work I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 21 seventeenth O
TAGTUPLE 1 until I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Aragon I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 9 Yugoslav I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 21 hire O
TAGTUPLE 1 Learning I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Figure I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 3 Hindenburg I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 19 royalty O
TAGTUPLE 3 Senators I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 albedo O
TAGTUPLE 6 unfavourable O
TAGTUPLE 153 routes O
TAGTUPLE 50 Armstrong I-PER
TAGTUPLE 15 Judgment I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 27 chariot O
TAGTUPLE 23 enthusiasts O
TAGTUPLE 1 Ghost I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Ganges I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Religious I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 13 judgments O
TAGTUPLE 1 Warrington I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 science I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 3 ELF I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 7 highest-ranking O
TAGTUPLE 2 + I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 12 deploying O
TAGTUPLE 94 praised O
TAGTUPLE 9 di O
TAGTUPLE 22 cello O
TAGTUPLE 4 Belgrano I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 3 Mildred I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Scarlet I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 Landscape I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 20 almonds O
TAGTUPLE 8 Grumman I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 370 helped O
TAGTUPLE 3 Camel I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 4 Veterinary I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 20 individually O
TAGTUPLE 2 Death I-PER
TAGTUPLE 195 borders O
TAGTUPLE 22 choices O
TAGTUPLE 5 Despoja I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 basal O
TAGTUPLE 75 charts O
TAGTUPLE 1 Aurora I-PER
TAGTUPLE 136 award O
TAGTUPLE 1 Ellison I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 Tactical I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 18 deposit O
TAGTUPLE 3 authorship I-PER
TAGTUPLE 3 Extreme O
TAGTUPLE 9 Considering O
TAGTUPLE 23 Magic I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 287 letters O
TAGTUPLE 88 joining O
TAGTUPLE 11 Beverly I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 21 Intelligence I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 21 Kahn I-PER
TAGTUPLE 7 1702 O
TAGTUPLE 5 tribunals O
TAGTUPLE 43 Symphony I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Boisbaudran I-PER
TAGTUPLE 11 2050 O
TAGTUPLE 6 Programmes I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 16 imperium O
TAGTUPLE 732 With O
TAGTUPLE 5 Indemnity I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 Pashtun I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Cow I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 13 <XXXd> I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 132 external O
TAGTUPLE 6 gentry O
TAGTUPLE 2 Paulo I-PER
TAGTUPLE 23 volcanoes O
TAGTUPLE 13 Qatar I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Haitian I-PER
TAGTUPLE 4 Economic I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 3 ANZAC I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 125 Hamlet I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 12 Titanic I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 fascination O
TAGTUPLE 6 Smith I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 17 Hits I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 24 Rotterdam I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 127 risk O
TAGTUPLE 16 compares O
TAGTUPLE 6 finalists O
TAGTUPLE 17 Edison I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Esther O
TAGTUPLE 6 90 I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 17 CSM I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Beatty I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 9 Bliss I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 misasagi O
TAGTUPLE 1 Sonny I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 <XXd> I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 Adolph I-PER
TAGTUPLE 19 Master O
TAGTUPLE 36 Adobe I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 18 maiden O
TAGTUPLE 1 outbreak I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 Potsdam I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 Berkshire I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 83 ignored O
TAGTUPLE 4 Fresh O
TAGTUPLE 11 normative O
TAGTUPLE 32 creates O
TAGTUPLE 3 Da I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Cináed I-PER
TAGTUPLE 11 successively O
TAGTUPLE 7 ASROC I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 27 east-west O
TAGTUPLE 24 dangers O
TAGTUPLE 7 extras O
TAGTUPLE 8 Tchaikovsky I-PER
TAGTUPLE 19 suspicious O
TAGTUPLE 33 125 O
TAGTUPLE 39 jerseys O
TAGTUPLE 1 Alabama O
TAGTUPLE 4 UN I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 unrivaled O
TAGTUPLE 12 Yōmei I-PER
TAGTUPLE 22 flesh O
TAGTUPLE 24 violation O
TAGTUPLE 45 Luis I-PER
TAGTUPLE 15 Halifax I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 9 Rises I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 3 Preston I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 19 resides O
TAGTUPLE 30 97 O
TAGTUPLE 6 League I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 8 Jaguar I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Cardinal I-PER
TAGTUPLE 39 1841 O
TAGTUPLE 9 pre-existing O
TAGTUPLE 183 Athens I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 Hanke I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 native I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 <XxXx> I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 26 confident O
TAGTUPLE 4 Heritage I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 ICRA I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 Warden I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 19 accusation O
TAGTUPLE 6 Melody I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 37 Computer I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 out I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 Henrietta I-PER
TAGTUPLE 55 39 O
TAGTUPLE 4 Pharsalus I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 Frédéric I-PER
TAGTUPLE 41 Leary I-PER
TAGTUPLE 11 Hot I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 Shoes I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Keyes I-PER
TAGTUPLE 13 Casimir I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 <XX-/Xdd> I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 15 worshipped O
TAGTUPLE 5 Aided O
TAGTUPLE 6 equitable O
TAGTUPLE 4 Sister I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 47 Rudolf I-PER
TAGTUPLE 24 hypnotism O
TAGTUPLE 5 Apollo-Soyuz I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 10 renounce O
TAGTUPLE 1 Malcolm I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 epics I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 13 Tamil I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 naming I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 108 afterwards O
TAGTUPLE 517 view O
TAGTUPLE 3 Bohemian I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Con I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 28 Now I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Beijing I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 61 Park I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 53 PlayStation I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 721 O
TAGTUPLE 22 Voivodeship I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 Moroni I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 all-black O
TAGTUPLE 7 670 O
TAGTUPLE 6 climactic O
TAGTUPLE 10 Motion I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 318 O
TAGTUPLE 6 bucket O
TAGTUPLE 78 scoring O
TAGTUPLE 7 John O
TAGTUPLE 101 at I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 29 Capra I-PER
TAGTUPLE 30 X I-PER
TAGTUPLE 15 sheer O
TAGTUPLE 2 Wolfman I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 14 armistice O
TAGTUPLE 6 unsafe O
TAGTUPLE 1 Fellow I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 42nd O
TAGTUPLE 19 terrible O
TAGTUPLE 475 College I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 57 encounter O
TAGTUPLE 19 mounting O
TAGTUPLE 6 artworks O
TAGTUPLE 293 <Xx-Xxx> I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 10 Pasadena I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 8 anti-communist O
TAGTUPLE 7 resorting O
TAGTUPLE 5 foreigner O
TAGTUPLE 35 improvised O
TAGTUPLE 7 scattering O
TAGTUPLE 11 Busey I-PER
TAGTUPLE 46 Patrick I-PER
TAGTUPLE 31 Museum I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 à O
TAGTUPLE 109 thereafter O
TAGTUPLE 1 Veronica I-PER
TAGTUPLE 19 Sybil I-PER
TAGTUPLE 10 bald O
TAGTUPLE 22 rendition O
TAGTUPLE 1 Sava I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 McClellan I-PER
TAGTUPLE 91 Rand I-PER
TAGTUPLE 18 copyrights O
TAGTUPLE 22 Irenaeus I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Model I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 needles O
TAGTUPLE 22 Beano I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 Bonn I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Rodin I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Goldwyn I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 13 purported O
TAGTUPLE 323 Islands I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 21 teammates O
TAGTUPLE 8 flowering O
TAGTUPLE 5 comprehensible O
TAGTUPLE 4 Pop O
TAGTUPLE 2 Orange I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 12 outlines O
TAGTUPLE 7 Miss O
TAGTUPLE 7 frog O
TAGTUPLE 41 broader O
TAGTUPLE 20 wounds O
TAGTUPLE 34 second-largest O
TAGTUPLE 11 Prefecture I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 25 south-west O
TAGTUPLE 1 Khrushchev I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 emulates O
TAGTUPLE 11 bays O
TAGTUPLE 124 advance O
TAGTUPLE 12 Roll I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 37 unitary O
TAGTUPLE 426 the I-PER
TAGTUPLE 41 justified O
TAGTUPLE 1 LP I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Allison I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 12 analyze O
TAGTUPLE 60 VII I-PER
TAGTUPLE 7 Holyrood I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 8 Provinces I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Norwich I-PER
TAGTUPLE 3 priority I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 16 Judea I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 Newer O
TAGTUPLE 3 eruption I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 8 meta-analysis O
TAGTUPLE 849 produced O
TAGTUPLE 297 decades O
TAGTUPLE 39 estates O
TAGTUPLE 8 choirs O
TAGTUPLE 2 movie I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 69 adoption O
TAGTUPLE 5 self-ownership O
TAGTUPLE 339 organization O
TAGTUPLE 41 indicating O
TAGTUPLE 25 Antioch I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 10 Earhart I-PER
TAGTUPLE 53 Centauri I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 Ranger I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 Jordan I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 646 League I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 Enola I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 9 1551 O
TAGTUPLE 1 Woods I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 Hadron I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 13 nightly O
TAGTUPLE 3 Marvel I-PER
TAGTUPLE 11 novelists O
TAGTUPLE 8 twenty-eight O
TAGTUPLE 13 lukewarm O
TAGTUPLE 19 Hamlin I-PER
TAGTUPLE 12 Comes I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 3 Finance O
TAGTUPLE 14 Croatia I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 former I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 7 Population O
TAGTUPLE 7 balloting O
TAGTUPLE 17 commuters O
TAGTUPLE 15 tract O
TAGTUPLE 9 Iran-Contra I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 Hammer I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 cyclist O
TAGTUPLE 22 Nationalist I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 126 contact O
TAGTUPLE 5 Harland I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 7 <x> I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 assurance O
TAGTUPLE 19 Drusus I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Dish I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 <d,d> I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 FIPS O
TAGTUPLE 44 fort O
TAGTUPLE 13 Parisian I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Claire I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 37 portray O
TAGTUPLE 8 Sawyer I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 9 Lasker I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 Commander I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 genitalia O
TAGTUPLE 5 internetworking O
TAGTUPLE 7 briefing O
TAGTUPLE 9 M I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 6-year O
TAGTUPLE 12 Before I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Infante I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 Baltic I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 Membership O
TAGTUPLE 41 Celtic I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Sylvia I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 7 streamlining O
TAGTUPLE 5 aerodrome O
TAGTUPLE 555 outside O
TAGTUPLE 63 verb O
TAGTUPLE 9 Utah I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 4169 two O
TAGTUPLE 12 Circassian I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 13 Charles I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 12 Anaxagoras I-PER
TAGTUPLE 4 Spain O
TAGTUPLE 10 Us I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 1560 O
TAGTUPLE 1 Babylonia I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Hurst I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 20 ISU I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 137 pitcher O
TAGTUPLE 14 retribution O
TAGTUPLE 2 Harlem I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 Deborah I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 francs O
TAGTUPLE 10 repertory O
TAGTUPLE 24 strife O
TAGTUPLE 121 traditions O
TAGTUPLE 1 Laws I-PER
TAGTUPLE 63 Republican I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 regained I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 Jacket I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 1147 O
TAGTUPLE 84 aim O
TAGTUPLE 2 Rich I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Parnell I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 170 Dr. O
TAGTUPLE 9 newcomers O
TAGTUPLE 57 Defense I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 4 Bing I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 699 once O
TAGTUPLE 6 Paz I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 Actium I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 10 Graduate I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 33 emblem O
TAGTUPLE 4 Stockton I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Outside I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 theses O
TAGTUPLE 2 Anne I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 19 World O
TAGTUPLE 13 Baker I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 7 primetime O
TAGTUPLE 8 Americans I-PER
TAGTUPLE 9 SNES I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 208 O
TAGTUPLE 544 art O
TAGTUPLE 14 stepping O
TAGTUPLE 35 exploited O
TAGTUPLE 22 strain O
TAGTUPLE 86 competitive O
TAGTUPLE 5 Brownson I-PER
TAGTUPLE 23 Mission I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 16 Titans I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 38 materialism O
TAGTUPLE 20 Conservation I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 10 Uribe I-PER
TAGTUPLE 10 exempted O
TAGTUPLE 29 Jesus I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 wakes O
TAGTUPLE 4 whites I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 40 IEC I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Pisa I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 27 marginal O
TAGTUPLE 198 Court I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Prize I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 19 revolutionized O
TAGTUPLE 1 Lloyd I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 terminally O
TAGTUPLE 12 spine O
TAGTUPLE 3 GBC I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 25 Olympus I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 Backman I-PER
TAGTUPLE 65 Acts I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 11 Dig I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 10 Schulz I-PER
TAGTUPLE 54 sixteen O
TAGTUPLE 51 traits O
TAGTUPLE 1 Chief I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 10 Raleigh I-PER
TAGTUPLE 15 colonialism O
TAGTUPLE 25 battlecruiser O
TAGTUPLE 26 Index I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 3 Idea I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 129 denied O
TAGTUPLE 3 Danny I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 23 Tao I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Settlement I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 13 Ashton I-PER
TAGTUPLE 93 Job I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 36 superhero O
TAGTUPLE 11 Daughter I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 28 predominant O
TAGTUPLE 5 Koufax I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 precipitously O
TAGTUPLE 6 NY I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 39 Hemisphere I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 4 <XXx> I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 deposition O
TAGTUPLE 13 Germany O
TAGTUPLE 13 120,000 O
TAGTUPLE 18 stereotypical O
TAGTUPLE 7 embracing O
TAGTUPLE 109 concerning O
TAGTUPLE 14 inlet O
TAGTUPLE 5 casus O
TAGTUPLE 59 Babylon I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 V. I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 guys O
TAGTUPLE 226 granted O
TAGTUPLE 2 Dog I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 3 Seed I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 Qin I-PER
TAGTUPLE 46 pounds O
TAGTUPLE 58 fitted O
TAGTUPLE 5 text I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Regulus I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 fewest O
TAGTUPLE 1 style I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 193 orders O
TAGTUPLE 10 Burghley I-PER
TAGTUPLE 3 Middle O
TAGTUPLE 15 Wisconsin I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 3 power I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Thurgood I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 Individual O
TAGTUPLE 1 Concorde I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 382 O
TAGTUPLE 14 Mary I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 3 AP I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 Killingworth I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 27 Pablo I-PER
TAGTUPLE 77 Rockies I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Points I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 520 club O
TAGTUPLE 12 disclose O
TAGTUPLE 1 Waterfront I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 Enraged O
TAGTUPLE 118 E. I-PER
TAGTUPLE 4 Hall O
TAGTUPLE 36 halted O
TAGTUPLE 46 phrases O
TAGTUPLE 2 Leigh I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 15 paranoia O
TAGTUPLE 55 preceding O
TAGTUPLE 13 Future I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 Round I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 116 A. I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 Ray I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 65 Research I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 </ddd> O
TAGTUPLE 3 Cash I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Agrippa I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 contour O
TAGTUPLE 6 good-natured O
TAGTUPLE 34 Mode I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 4 Palace I-PER
TAGTUPLE 31 Chandler I-PER
TAGTUPLE 19 Tribune I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 22 system I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 Very I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 silicon O
TAGTUPLE 14 Janata I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 7 Players I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 dualist O
TAGTUPLE 17 wheels O
TAGTUPLE 33 sexuality O
TAGTUPLE 350 Jewish I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 35 nervous O
TAGTUPLE 6 pedagogical O
TAGTUPLE 2 underworld I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 Hartley I-PER
TAGTUPLE 192 generation O
TAGTUPLE 6 2100 O
TAGTUPLE 18 DOM I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 93 and I-PER
TAGTUPLE 243 railway O
TAGTUPLE 33 Arnaz I-PER
TAGTUPLE 209 format O
TAGTUPLE 185 improved O
TAGTUPLE 9 Trammell I-PER
TAGTUPLE 10 WHO I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 96 illegal O
TAGTUPLE 4 department I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 Monsanto I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 4 O'Connell I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 All I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 Blows I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Candy I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 12 uproar O
TAGTUPLE 2 Lantern I-PER
TAGTUPLE 11 Stars I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Simpson I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 11 riches O
TAGTUPLE 48 strings O
TAGTUPLE 5 mitzvot O
TAGTUPLE 17 comparisons O
TAGTUPLE 5 Kanem I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 9 remedies O
TAGTUPLE 25 1791 O
TAGTUPLE 17 Window I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Gore I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 12 Elevation O
TAGTUPLE 1177 modern O
TAGTUPLE 3 Libertarian O
TAGTUPLE 234 That O
TAGTUPLE 5 parole O
TAGTUPLE 4 Wear I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 35 Lennon I-PER
TAGTUPLE 38 Don I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 underestimate O
TAGTUPLE 2 1958 I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 13 Mirage I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 initiative I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 SE I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 14 collaborate O
TAGTUPLE 7 republished O
TAGTUPLE 33 paramilitary O
TAGTUPLE 11 Aveiro I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 8 Salisbury I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Griffin I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Yeager I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 7 Millay I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 plaintext O
TAGTUPLE 1 Minh I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 Mode I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 3 Band I-PER
TAGTUPLE 10 FG I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Weil I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 24 1827 O
TAGTUPLE 33 clay O
TAGTUPLE 1 Just I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Skeptical I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 36 V I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Wall O
TAGTUPLE 442 attempt O
TAGTUPLE 17 climatic O
TAGTUPLE 18 Jennings I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 communism I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Capitalism O
TAGTUPLE 100 Cleveland I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 Fe I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 87 category O
TAGTUPLE 12 Historic I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 Is I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 8 Darfur I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Monsters I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 4 mm I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 diocese I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 1970 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 15 spark O
TAGTUPLE 204 vehicles O
TAGTUPLE 3 PGA I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 4 Lily I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 <xx-.dxx> O
TAGTUPLE 2 Brescia I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 34 900 O
TAGTUPLE 10 fixing O
TAGTUPLE 1 Tulsa I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 chaste O
TAGTUPLE 7 Graciosa I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 7 impatient O
TAGTUPLE 2 Ecuador I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 83 intense O
TAGTUPLE 230 Even O
TAGTUPLE 4 Stanford I-PER
TAGTUPLE 40 <Xx-Xxx> O
TAGTUPLE 20 mistakes O
TAGTUPLE 5 deep-water O
TAGTUPLE 12 reinforcement O
TAGTUPLE 2 Thal I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 90 believes O
TAGTUPLE 1 </x./x/> O
TAGTUPLE 15 optimization O
TAGTUPLE 15 frigate O
TAGTUPLE 4 Auckland I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 kindness O
TAGTUPLE 10 sloop O
TAGTUPLE 10 McGraw I-PER
TAGTUPLE 16 UK I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 175 environment O
TAGTUPLE 11 Older O
TAGTUPLE 15 protectorate O
TAGTUPLE 9 27,000 O
TAGTUPLE 5 vehement O
TAGTUPLE 72 Hopkins I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 Malachi I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 Mix I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 20 nurse O
TAGTUPLE 1 Manchu I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 59 mystery O
TAGTUPLE 2 Mine I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 29 Ga. I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Bailey I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 18 serpent O
TAGTUPLE 31 economist O
TAGTUPLE 13 resentment O
TAGTUPLE 207 operation O
TAGTUPLE 1 <dd-dd> I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 3 barrier I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 28 justification O
TAGTUPLE 5 Scribonia I-PER
TAGTUPLE 13 Brian I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 98 Vienna I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 12 Hindu I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 problems I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 47 imagery O
TAGTUPLE 6 Buell I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 8 Wally I-PER
TAGTUPLE 15 touched O
TAGTUPLE 14 coveted O
TAGTUPLE 2 Fédération I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 282 1974 O
TAGTUPLE 13 Mandela I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Buell I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Chaitin I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 1573 O
TAGTUPLE 21 longitude O
TAGTUPLE 5 primates O
TAGTUPLE 2 Sixteen I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 26 cassette O
TAGTUPLE 114 revenue O
TAGTUPLE 10 sceptical O
TAGTUPLE 22 quietly O
TAGTUPLE 1 <Xx:Xxx> I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Jeux I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 11 Mayer I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Halle I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 Cap I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Sisters I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 9 free-market O
TAGTUPLE 4 Clyde I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 12 Leno I-PER
TAGTUPLE 21240 ( O
TAGTUPLE 1 Siddeley I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 25 Forum I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 30 physicians O
TAGTUPLE 4 Communists I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 10 driest O
TAGTUPLE 169 pieces O
TAGTUPLE 12 Mint I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 24 bacteria O
TAGTUPLE 81 travelled O
TAGTUPLE 68 eliminated O
TAGTUPLE 15 5.2 O
TAGTUPLE 2272 year O
TAGTUPLE 6 slash O
TAGTUPLE 5 Movies O
TAGTUPLE 9 Enterprises I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 16 incompatible O
TAGTUPLE 53 stepped O
TAGTUPLE 28 Straczynski I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 republican I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 10 procedural O
TAGTUPLE 30 Player I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 12 DJ O
TAGTUPLE 11 fifties O
TAGTUPLE 9 Gothenburg I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 Alfaro I-PER
TAGTUPLE 16 spearheaded O
TAGTUPLE 13 Cope I-PER
TAGTUPLE 13 constructs O
TAGTUPLE 201 1961 O
TAGTUPLE 2 gardens I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 87 verse O
TAGTUPLE 38 Grinnell I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 8 Indonesian I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 McFarlane I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 797 O
TAGTUPLE 1 Detective O
TAGTUPLE 13 rapids O
TAGTUPLE 21 Dalhousie I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 8 Minsk I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 41 crop O
TAGTUPLE 3 Vivian I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1585 population O
TAGTUPLE 14 disclosed O
TAGTUPLE 5 Hellespont I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 7 Cocteau I-PER
TAGTUPLE 13 Burnett I-PER
TAGTUPLE 35 continuously O
TAGTUPLE 1 labour I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 20 Amitabh I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 Nassau I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 92 Darwin I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 theorem I-PER
TAGTUPLE 33 Conn. I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 34 inadequate O
TAGTUPLE 652 William I-PER
TAGTUPLE 45 northwestern O
TAGTUPLE 9 Alexius I-PER
TAGTUPLE 10 militarily O
TAGTUPLE 1 Schmidt I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 renders O
TAGTUPLE 1 Silver O
TAGTUPLE 5 anthem I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 Controversy O
TAGTUPLE 388 9 O
TAGTUPLE 82 Abd I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Nin I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 15 eroded O
TAGTUPLE 6 Pruitt I-PER
TAGTUPLE 14 overseen O
TAGTUPLE 5 MLC I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 day I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Seeking I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 63 United I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 intervention I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 3 PGA O
TAGTUPLE 21 F4U I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 45 </x/> O
TAGTUPLE 266 food O
TAGTUPLE 33 dish O
TAGTUPLE 72 weekly O
TAGTUPLE 1141 become O
TAGTUPLE 1 Muhammad I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 7 fund-raising O
TAGTUPLE 5 Anhui I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 9 Lies I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 182 Valley I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 102 try O
TAGTUPLE 5 Huerta I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Maps O
TAGTUPLE 4 Seminole I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Paraguay I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 7 Flores I-PER
TAGTUPLE 3 Yorktown I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 15 emancipation O
TAGTUPLE 9 Musée I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 9 choreography O
TAGTUPLE 9 projectile O
TAGTUPLE 9 Barbarian I-PER
TAGTUPLE 7 photographers O
TAGTUPLE 211 policies O
TAGTUPLE 1 Anand I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 campaign I-PER
TAGTUPLE 58 signal O
TAGTUPLE 5 Jim I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 126 damage O
TAGTUPLE 17 Contrary O
TAGTUPLE 2 Sweden I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 349 for I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 3 Plowman I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 19 curling O
TAGTUPLE 5 Moveable I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 Modern I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 20 Tramlink I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 7 costing O
TAGTUPLE 83 ideal O
TAGTUPLE 44 Cummings I-PER
TAGTUPLE 21 Duncan I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 Slavery O
TAGTUPLE 10 Manila I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 Solution I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Lesser I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 internationals O
TAGTUPLE 1 Tennant I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 21 Coleco I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 7 Wallis I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Empress I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 3 Coleco I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Yates I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Stockton I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 LED O
TAGTUPLE 3 championship I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 cabal O
TAGTUPLE 12 Yer I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 18 Little I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 guaranteeing O
TAGTUPLE 32 personalities O
TAGTUPLE 13 Weimar I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 departmental O
TAGTUPLE 7 collects O
TAGTUPLE 4 1924 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 Congregation I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Bishops O
TAGTUPLE 1 Giovanni I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 MiG-29 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 14 ballads O
TAGTUPLE 6 Mahatma I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 Qaghan I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Plaza I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 20 Palestrina I-PER
TAGTUPLE 19 Aargau I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 half I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 Urey I-PER
TAGTUPLE 9 Bennington I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 24 exchanges O
TAGTUPLE 7 Konoe I-PER
TAGTUPLE 10 Youth I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 bowed O
TAGTUPLE 14 IDEA I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 Ike I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 14 Slavs I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 17 defendant O
TAGTUPLE 1 Dog I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 8 Fight I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 nation I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 Ahern I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 1221 O
TAGTUPLE 59 pitched O
TAGTUPLE 1 Chaldean O
TAGTUPLE 13 Arminius I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Fortress I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 8 Edmonton I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 82 talent O
TAGTUPLE 281 destroyed O
TAGTUPLE 3 Poudre I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 23 Pennsylvania I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 spelt O
TAGTUPLE 6 funky O
TAGTUPLE 17 questioning O
TAGTUPLE 5 49,000 O
TAGTUPLE 2 Steiner I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 1,400 O
TAGTUPLE 14 geyser O
TAGTUPLE 5 frowned O
TAGTUPLE 9 Branch I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 184 distance O
TAGTUPLE 20 Doctor I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 Lithuanian I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 anachronistic O
TAGTUPLE 195 1930s O
TAGTUPLE 15 resistant O
TAGTUPLE 7 bodyguards O
TAGTUPLE 48 lifted O
TAGTUPLE 54 necessity O
TAGTUPLE 1 Bayezid I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Martín I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 18 Galaxy I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 24 ads O
TAGTUPLE 5 1261 O
TAGTUPLE 7 bells O
TAGTUPLE 1 Pants I-PER
TAGTUPLE 62 2000s O
TAGTUPLE 24 ace O
TAGTUPLE 7 SAC I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 11 abbots O
TAGTUPLE 207 Darwin I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Dionysus I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 7 deadlocked O
TAGTUPLE 2 Ninja I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 54 Tucker I-PER
TAGTUPLE 10 Included O
TAGTUPLE 8 fall I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Vertol I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 7 Secretary-General O
TAGTUPLE 201 Germany I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 <XxXx> I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Magnus I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 metaphorical O
TAGTUPLE 1 gay I-PER
TAGTUPLE 7 dictatorships O
TAGTUPLE 20 Weekly I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Neve I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 Pavel I-PER
TAGTUPLE 393 mainly O
TAGTUPLE 10 Duke I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 UAW I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 Gameboy I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 history I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Vertol I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 1598 O
TAGTUPLE 9 Hammer I-PER
TAGTUPLE 71 recalled O
TAGTUPLE 3 Preston I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 99 1905 O
TAGTUPLE 3 Abilene I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 bibliography I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 154 O
TAGTUPLE 6 plasma O
TAGTUPLE 10 relational O
TAGTUPLE 7 Layla I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Game I-PER
TAGTUPLE 4 Link I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Wan I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 21 recounted O
TAGTUPLE 39 intact O
TAGTUPLE 5 Indy I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 12 Panjshir I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 36 32-bit O
TAGTUPLE 4 Djibouti I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 Newspapers O
TAGTUPLE 24 Werner I-PER
TAGTUPLE 19 placement O
TAGTUPLE 5 Nelson I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Cup I-PER
TAGTUPLE 39 Electric I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 reclassified O
TAGTUPLE 1 N. I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 10 Riddler I-PER
TAGTUPLE 4 80386 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 210 combat O
TAGTUPLE 248 kilometres O
TAGTUPLE 5 Americans I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 need I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Phillies I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Group I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 Sudan I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 70 suspected O
TAGTUPLE 12 Alone I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 3 River I-PER
TAGTUPLE 44 destroying O
TAGTUPLE 3 ε O
TAGTUPLE 4 international I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 26 Brittany I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 10 EBCDIC O
TAGTUPLE 16 psychoanalysis O
TAGTUPLE 13 acquaintances O
TAGTUPLE 84 picked O
TAGTUPLE 8 8.2 O
TAGTUPLE 18 Film O
TAGTUPLE 7 rope O
TAGTUPLE 6 Belorussian I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 Cowes I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 26 endangered O
TAGTUPLE 17 textual O
TAGTUPLE 5 criticise O
TAGTUPLE 1 NSU I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 13 Lake I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 levied O
TAGTUPLE 1 Boulogne I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 53 impressive O
TAGTUPLE 4 gas I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 7 Passenger O
TAGTUPLE 3 <xx-x-> O
TAGTUPLE 17 expectation O
TAGTUPLE 1 Genoa I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Disease I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 46 watershed O
TAGTUPLE 1 1854 I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 156 O
TAGTUPLE 5 presides O
TAGTUPLE 1 Walter I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 Muslim I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 Dumnonii I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 15 soprano O
TAGTUPLE 5 parlor O
TAGTUPLE 29 molecular O
TAGTUPLE 55 nevertheless O
TAGTUPLE 7 Bayer I-PER
TAGTUPLE 10 empresses O
TAGTUPLE 7 sur I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Alba I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 7 cage O
TAGTUPLE 43 Manuel I-PER
TAGTUPLE 31 timber O
TAGTUPLE 17 catching O
TAGTUPLE 41 possessions O
TAGTUPLE 4 Fleischmann O
TAGTUPLE 15 chiropractors O
TAGTUPLE 149 southeast O
TAGTUPLE 2 number I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 roadway O
TAGTUPLE 184 daily O
TAGTUPLE 2 Meteor I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 11 luminaries O
TAGTUPLE 15 textbooks O
TAGTUPLE 3 Ski I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Naismith I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 3 Kettering I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 3 pact I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 134 17th O
TAGTUPLE 6 Leland I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 sabbatical O
TAGTUPLE 5 unknowingly O
TAGTUPLE 1 <X../Xxx> O
TAGTUPLE 1 Bailey O
TAGTUPLE 1 Abraxas O
TAGTUPLE 1 Ram I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 19 Hungarian I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 36 Tennessee I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 4 DD I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 microcomputers O
TAGTUPLE 60 zones O
TAGTUPLE 6 Sir I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 congress I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 41 lit O
TAGTUPLE 56 highlands O
TAGTUPLE 2 Frank I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 4 Francis I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Res I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 19 Go I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 HP I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 65 inherited O
TAGTUPLE 6 carbine O
TAGTUPLE 1 Leo I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 regulators O
TAGTUPLE 4 P. I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 Very I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 Trent I-PER
TAGTUPLE 44 disastrous O
TAGTUPLE 18 Mrs. O
TAGTUPLE 20 Rockefeller I-PER
TAGTUPLE 13 nuns O
TAGTUPLE 2 Pendragon I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 Fifth I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 19 crossover O
TAGTUPLE 1 Celt I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 cantilever O
TAGTUPLE 113 thinking O
TAGTUPLE 154 cross O
TAGTUPLE 1 tool I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 216 O
TAGTUPLE 16 Economic I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 Sisters I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Manual I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 Thom I-PER
TAGTUPLE 9 auditorium O
TAGTUPLE 23 2005 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 270 attempts O
TAGTUPLE 1 Krishna I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 16 Isle I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 29 Reynolds I-PER
TAGTUPLE 497 movement O
TAGTUPLE 6 relentless O
TAGTUPLE 9 radioactivity O
TAGTUPLE 36 dances O
TAGTUPLE 1 Musical O
TAGTUPLE 13 optics O
TAGTUPLE 4 northeast I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 9 majorities O
TAGTUPLE 14 folding O
TAGTUPLE 28 screens O
TAGTUPLE 6 BBWAA I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 20 encourages O
TAGTUPLE 34 traders O
TAGTUPLE 1 fathers I-PER
TAGTUPLE 11 Hook I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 7 affinities O
TAGTUPLE 10 pickup O
TAGTUPLE 295 creation O
TAGTUPLE 36 Assyrian I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 22 Stones I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 7 anomaly O
TAGTUPLE 2 hovercraft I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 <xx-xx> I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 8 Tennō I-PER
TAGTUPLE 4 Luther I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 frontline O
TAGTUPLE 6 legend I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 naturalism O
TAGTUPLE 2 Stafford I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 24 Isabella I-PER
TAGTUPLE 216 route O
TAGTUPLE 30 enlarged O
TAGTUPLE 269 reference O
TAGTUPLE 5 Bela I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 Code I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 charter I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Mormon O
TAGTUPLE 2 Countries I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Caliph I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 3 <Xx/xd> I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Guard I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 <X++dx> I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 20 Milwaukee I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 34 counts O
TAGTUPLE 4 Lilly I-PER
TAGTUPLE 298 ordered O
TAGTUPLE 14 cleaning O
TAGTUPLE 4 Architecture I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 13 elders O
TAGTUPLE 18 insights O
TAGTUPLE 12 Antinous I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 Junior I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 244 activity O
TAGTUPLE 11 reestablish O
TAGTUPLE 20 Camp I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Esperanto I-PER
TAGTUPLE 109 cavalry O
TAGTUPLE 2 Door I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 Via I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Idle I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Grey O
TAGTUPLE 5 recommending O
TAGTUPLE 7 hedonistic O
TAGTUPLE 6 imitators O
TAGTUPLE 2 71 I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 conspiracy I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 blaming O
TAGTUPLE 1 Craig I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 38 stationed O
TAGTUPLE 42 upgraded O
TAGTUPLE 6 yd O
TAGTUPLE 12 sorties O
TAGTUPLE 13 rolls O
TAGTUPLE 24 imagined O
TAGTUPLE 2 rules I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Oaks I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 54 consent O
TAGTUPLE 19 heightened O
TAGTUPLE 7 Toussaint I-PER
TAGTUPLE 55 permit O
TAGTUPLE 2 <dd,> O
TAGTUPLE 4 <X-X> I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 12 Franklin I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 field I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 27 specialist O
TAGTUPLE 3 Electricity I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Barlow I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 29 ancestor O
TAGTUPLE 21 Hausa I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 Parthian I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 9 lured O
TAGTUPLE 170 suggests O
TAGTUPLE 55 Baltimore I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 E I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 Manchu I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Midland I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 EEOC I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 56 nobility O
TAGTUPLE 6 Hellman I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 off I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 48 prose O
TAGTUPLE 31 grid O
TAGTUPLE 1 treat I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Thornton I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 Oxus I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 <dddd> I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 basketball I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 59 dealt O
TAGTUPLE 18 admirers O
TAGTUPLE 25 brutal O
TAGTUPLE 1 <xxx.> I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 8 venerable O
TAGTUPLE 24 arise O
TAGTUPLE 6 418 O
TAGTUPLE 8 overcoming O
TAGTUPLE 1 Smithsonian I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 7 lean O
TAGTUPLE 1 Tor I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 4 Fighting O
TAGTUPLE 7 Ma I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 disuse O
TAGTUPLE 7 1620 O
TAGTUPLE 19 amended O
TAGTUPLE 51 Yale I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 lurid O
TAGTUPLE 217 leave O
TAGTUPLE 1 scandals I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Huxley I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 3 Guzmán I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 Andreas I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 conflict I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Applied I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 616 O
TAGTUPLE 11 heels O
TAGTUPLE 1 Leyte I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 15 breakup O
TAGTUPLE 5 23,000 O
TAGTUPLE 8 Skåne I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 14 Trail I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 433 I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 58 passages O
TAGTUPLE 44 stronger O
TAGTUPLE 46 acquire O
TAGTUPLE 41 tram O
TAGTUPLE 23 runner O
TAGTUPLE 21 Returning O
TAGTUPLE 10 Jaguars I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 147 Hughes I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Gigi I-PER
TAGTUPLE 4 Gentlemen I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 11 islands I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 10 Everton I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 7 unnecessarily O
TAGTUPLE 54 IMF I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 façade O
TAGTUPLE 2 estate I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 Mosul I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Chari I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 <xxdxd> O
TAGTUPLE 121 satellite O
TAGTUPLE 7 8.9 O
TAGTUPLE 28 ambitions O
TAGTUPLE 2 MK I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Cowes I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 76 compiler O
TAGTUPLE 29 prehistoric O
TAGTUPLE 16 Tsvangirai I-PER
TAGTUPLE 12 Speed I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 104 walls O
TAGTUPLE 2 Yi I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 13 sonatas O
TAGTUPLE 1 Murders I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Merrick I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 32 guilt O
TAGTUPLE 2 Moro I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 1919 I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 8 McDowell I-PER
TAGTUPLE 52 revision O
TAGTUPLE 12 cursed O
TAGTUPLE 10 forgiveness O
TAGTUPLE 16 Get I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 10 unsolved O
TAGTUPLE 42 portable O
TAGTUPLE 7 IOI I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 10 Gosford I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 4 Estes I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 Backwoods I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 27 exacerbated O
TAGTUPLE 11 attendants O
TAGTUPLE 7 Thinker I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 39 Jan I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 Money O
TAGTUPLE 5 Afrika I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Collection O
TAGTUPLE 2 Alpine I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 3 <dd.:dd> O
TAGTUPLE 2 its I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 allegorical I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 22 exceed O
TAGTUPLE 7 Haiti I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 30 Control I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 12 signifying O
TAGTUPLE 1 <X,,XX> O
TAGTUPLE 6 probabilities O
TAGTUPLE 216 increasing O
TAGTUPLE 14 Beyond I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 9 quanta O
TAGTUPLE 123 piano O
TAGTUPLE 27 overtime O
TAGTUPLE 3 cricket I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Each I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 navigation I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 11 Sipe I-PER
TAGTUPLE 9 seeming O
TAGTUPLE 27 reliance O
TAGTUPLE 23 Immanuel I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 Kingdoms I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 17 Jezebel I-PER
TAGTUPLE 20 rites O
TAGTUPLE 9 Edwin I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 8.6 O
TAGTUPLE 59 Green I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Stockholm I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 113 NBC I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 culture I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 11 escorts O
TAGTUPLE 1 Gustavus I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 19 Sayyaf I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 4 Whitgift I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Kelly I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 10 Ethan I-PER
TAGTUPLE 136 agencies O
TAGTUPLE 4 Marburg I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 70 distant O
TAGTUPLE 6 cathedrals O
TAGTUPLE 9 Visitors O
TAGTUPLE 8 lighthouse O
TAGTUPLE 106 1935 O
TAGTUPLE 9 Hester I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 Wiley I-PER
TAGTUPLE 12 Morning I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 Valderrama I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 inscriptions I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 15 swear O
TAGTUPLE 28 accumulated O
TAGTUPLE 26 Contemporary O
TAGTUPLE 2 Iona I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 Schelling I-PER
TAGTUPLE 12 bankers O
TAGTUPLE 1 Doing O
TAGTUPLE 5 Gneisenau I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Stray I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 3 Victory I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 <Xx.XX> I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Lion I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 27 Exxon I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 24 Warsaw I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 4 Americas I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 74 error O
TAGTUPLE 1 Ernest I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 Von O
TAGTUPLE 44 collecting O
TAGTUPLE 8 Attorney I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 27 Richardson I-PER
TAGTUPLE 112 partner O
TAGTUPLE 1 poet I-PER
TAGTUPLE 28 Will I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 Lycée I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 25 Cox I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 Kazan I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 119 diplomatic O
TAGTUPLE 43 Hades I-PER
TAGTUPLE 9 Christians O
TAGTUPLE 5 Sir I-PER
TAGTUPLE 30 performs O
TAGTUPLE 1 Jimmy I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 12 Comic I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 13 Buck I-PER
TAGTUPLE 41 Athletic I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 33 Andhra I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 7 centaurs O
TAGTUPLE 25 geometrical O
TAGTUPLE 45 athletic O
TAGTUPLE 1 Sound O
TAGTUPLE 17 illustrator O
TAGTUPLE 5 378 O
TAGTUPLE 10 unjust O
TAGTUPLE 6 Mstislav I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 readership O
TAGTUPLE 9 Shiv I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Tongan I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 8 unto O
TAGTUPLE 4 belief I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 egalitarian O
TAGTUPLE 3 Stephens I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 20 preached O
TAGTUPLE 19 Gerard I-PER
TAGTUPLE 7 TfL I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 Rushdie I-PER
TAGTUPLE 17 Cossacks I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 23 reinforce O
TAGTUPLE 18 dementia O
TAGTUPLE 4 Kenyon I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Boswell I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 146 philosopher O
TAGTUPLE 36 consonant O
TAGTUPLE 26 promises O
TAGTUPLE 3 vita O
TAGTUPLE 5 demos O
TAGTUPLE 182 reality O
TAGTUPLE 2 <XXdd> I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 10 Borromini I-PER
TAGTUPLE 29 decrease O
TAGTUPLE 194 ? O
TAGTUPLE 5 <dd,dxx> O
TAGTUPLE 7 underlined O
TAGTUPLE 28 malaria O
TAGTUPLE 77 dynamic O
TAGTUPLE 15 coordinator O
TAGTUPLE 7 Shan I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 delegations O
TAGTUPLE 22 waned O
TAGTUPLE 6 Etna I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 23 interact O
TAGTUPLE 2 Ferdinand I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 4 Åmål I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 Hölderlin I-PER
TAGTUPLE 7 296 O
TAGTUPLE 5 Produced O
TAGTUPLE 43 streams O
TAGTUPLE 5 instantaneous O
TAGTUPLE 58 genuine O
TAGTUPLE 218 Bill I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 Kowloon I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1737 so O
TAGTUPLE 3 Computing I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 13 benign O
TAGTUPLE 1 Settlers O
TAGTUPLE 46 barely O
TAGTUPLE 5 raid I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 127 resigned O
TAGTUPLE 1 plane I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 3 Presidency I-PER
TAGTUPLE 27 centred O
TAGTUPLE 2 IndyCar I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 4 Adrianople I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 14 punish O
TAGTUPLE 7 decade-long O
TAGTUPLE 6 BAE I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 fire I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 4 resurrection I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 61 arrangements O
TAGTUPLE 5 impressionist O
TAGTUPLE 241 female O
TAGTUPLE 11 directory O
TAGTUPLE 1 is I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 7 Brigid I-PER
TAGTUPLE 33 1818 O
TAGTUPLE 29 north-east O
TAGTUPLE 2384 world O
TAGTUPLE 9 benefactor O
TAGTUPLE 39 racism O
TAGTUPLE 15 Woodrow I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Seymour I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 15 Theory I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 Schiphol I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 15 1716 O
TAGTUPLE 37 terrestrial O
TAGTUPLE 16 Donegal I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 464 Park I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 17 Humphry I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 Mass I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Barbie I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 19 mound O
TAGTUPLE 10 Ally I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 11 emulators O
TAGTUPLE 553 India I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 Iron I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 8 bush O
TAGTUPLE 5 Augustinian I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 10 Wagoner I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 MDC I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 31 agrees O
TAGTUPLE 144 Zappa I-PER
TAGTUPLE 10 north-eastern O
TAGTUPLE 35 sheet O
TAGTUPLE 6 then-President O
TAGTUPLE 1 Trucks I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 19 teenager O
TAGTUPLE 5 Rocky I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 naked-eye O
TAGTUPLE 22 Naval I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 <xx-Xx> I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 8 Christy I-PER
TAGTUPLE 9 optimal O
TAGTUPLE 18 Philipp I-PER
TAGTUPLE 10 Curie I-PER
TAGTUPLE 11 Disney I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Priory I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Astros I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 70 bed O
TAGTUPLE 5 3.11 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 29 repeat O
TAGTUPLE 3 Oil I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 9 50 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 50 withdrawn O
TAGTUPLE 5 discrepancy O
TAGTUPLE 6 <x/xx> O
TAGTUPLE 213 definition O
TAGTUPLE 8 Noyce I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 Kershaw I-PER
TAGTUPLE 3 Saul I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 14 disregard O
TAGTUPLE 239 consists O
TAGTUPLE 9 437 O
TAGTUPLE 6 combating O
TAGTUPLE 93 conclusion O
TAGTUPLE 2 Sporting I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 20 resurgence O
TAGTUPLE 23 Edinburgh I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Chapter I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 21 maturity O
TAGTUPLE 16 Nebraska I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 81 Davenport I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 14 Arab-Israeli I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Darlington I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 whistle O
TAGTUPLE 14 Schilling I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 <dddx,> O
TAGTUPLE 7 identifiers O
TAGTUPLE 225 royal O
TAGTUPLE 3 Derry I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Britons I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 girl I-PER
TAGTUPLE 7 doses O
TAGTUPLE 41 2008 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 18 Theron I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 respectability O
TAGTUPLE 1 Laplace I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 seasons I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 391 <Xxx> I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Lothar I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Che I-PER
TAGTUPLE 14 conveyed O
TAGTUPLE 5 Lion I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 care I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Butler I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 26 sing O
TAGTUPLE 1 between I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 3 Patton I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 15 livery O
TAGTUPLE 15 Hogan I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Boroughs I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 Changes I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 74 ESA I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Ravenna I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 mistletoe O
TAGTUPLE 15 <xx'xx> O
TAGTUPLE 37 supersonic O
TAGTUPLE 30 Scheer I-PER
TAGTUPLE 12 disability O
TAGTUPLE 43 illustrated O
TAGTUPLE 14 Sosa I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Sometimes I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 crusades O
TAGTUPLE 157 ball O
TAGTUPLE 20 thinks O
TAGTUPLE 5 Scrooge I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 16 interstate O
TAGTUPLE 1 anarchists I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 Zeno I-PER
TAGTUPLE 73 consequences O
TAGTUPLE 9 1737 O
TAGTUPLE 16 underwater O
TAGTUPLE 15 ascend O
TAGTUPLE 6 Whitney I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 35 Ed I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 political I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 Turner I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 593 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 <XX/XX> O
TAGTUPLE 13 partition O
TAGTUPLE 1 Banff I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 decimated O
TAGTUPLE 9 recurrence O
TAGTUPLE 1 Enterprises I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 polynomials O
TAGTUPLE 62 Armenian I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 235 Sweden I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 HD I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 35 shirt O
TAGTUPLE 15 telephony O
TAGTUPLE 13 subsidiaries O
TAGTUPLE 2 Daily O
TAGTUPLE 11 prostate O
TAGTUPLE 4 Aldus I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 10 secede O
TAGTUPLE 6 Como I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 26 Ricky I-PER
TAGTUPLE 3 Rich O
TAGTUPLE 38 flooding O
TAGTUPLE 29 Accordingly O
TAGTUPLE 4 PAN I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 quantified O
TAGTUPLE 2 Teutonic I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 9 O'Toole I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Salmon O
TAGTUPLE 13 superpower O
TAGTUPLE 1 Important I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Count I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Tenji O
TAGTUPLE 5 terrorist I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 59 Little I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 68 exploration O
TAGTUPLE 5 Genoshan I-PER
TAGTUPLE 59 storyline O
TAGTUPLE 5 Constellation I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 SRI I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 21 collegiate O
TAGTUPLE 5 Nemo I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Cinema O
TAGTUPLE 35 book I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 38 feat O
TAGTUPLE 9 legalized O
TAGTUPLE 64 missing O
TAGTUPLE 39 Regional I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 7 35 I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 4 <Xd+dd> I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 44 Cromwell I-PER
TAGTUPLE 63 Jeff I-PER
TAGTUPLE 7 Fine I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 avenged O
TAGTUPLE 1 Triangle I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 10 Gradually O
TAGTUPLE 9 Estimates O
TAGTUPLE 5 Bobbio I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 recurred O
TAGTUPLE 1 Countries I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 3 1-2-3 O
TAGTUPLE 1 Horde I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Tamil I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 3 Performing I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 20 Amos I-PER
TAGTUPLE 13 alumnus O
TAGTUPLE 3 Monthly I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Andalusia I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 throne I-PER
TAGTUPLE 13 final I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 Rope I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 tutoring O
TAGTUPLE 50 Nicholas I-PER
TAGTUPLE 16 Diane I-PER
TAGTUPLE 3 computers I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Fargo I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 18th I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 4 Prince I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Plate I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 188 Guinea I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 4 Birch I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Random I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 16 Cordillera I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 Française I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 Glass I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 21 genes O
TAGTUPLE 2 Corp. I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 Whiteman I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 Analysis O
TAGTUPLE 6 've I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 then-current O
TAGTUPLE 4 geography I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Ken I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 4 A.C. I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 Arthur I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 10 Nicole I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 destroyed I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Kush I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 Yalta I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 sports I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 617 natural O
TAGTUPLE 150 Batman I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 Otto I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 Folkestone I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 al-Aqsa I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Monteverdi I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 1995 I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Ajax I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 downwards O
TAGTUPLE 1 Gould I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 deportation O
TAGTUPLE 6 Fertile I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Dean I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 44 row O
TAGTUPLE 12 typed O
TAGTUPLE 16 entrenched O
TAGTUPLE 1 Pin I-PER
TAGTUPLE 11 pardoned O
TAGTUPLE 7 Pirithous I-PER
TAGTUPLE 10 Enlightenment I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 41 deny O
TAGTUPLE 13 depressions O
TAGTUPLE 2 Facility I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 vice-presidential O
TAGTUPLE 2 Savoy I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 50 Odyssey I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 have I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Daytona I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 miraculously O
TAGTUPLE 34 graduating O
TAGTUPLE 218 aspects O
TAGTUPLE 6 Iranian I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 9 uniformitarianism O
TAGTUPLE 3 industry I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 8 boast O
TAGTUPLE 10 anonymously O
TAGTUPLE 5 Booth I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 9 Yale I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 D.C. I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 232 raised O
TAGTUPLE 6 foreshadowing O
TAGTUPLE 9 agony O
TAGTUPLE 9 perihelion O
TAGTUPLE 1 Durand I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 prerogative O
TAGTUPLE 82 600 O
TAGTUPLE 1 Río I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Glasgow I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 12 differentiation O
TAGTUPLE 5 counter-terrorism O
TAGTUPLE 7 Austrian I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 7 swelled O
TAGTUPLE 2 <\x\x> O
TAGTUPLE 1 train I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 203 removed O
TAGTUPLE 1 armistice I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 P I-PER
TAGTUPLE 82 phase O
TAGTUPLE 2 Lanka I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 friar O
TAGTUPLE 1 al-Aqsa I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 Cast O
TAGTUPLE 1 Tenerife I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 9 1767 O
TAGTUPLE 115 Max I-PER
TAGTUPLE 39 Council I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 10 doctorates O
TAGTUPLE 1 Resurrection I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Woods I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 16 Letters I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Monarchy I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 8 ACF I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 32 Rossini I-PER
TAGTUPLE 7 Darien I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 8 hotspot O
TAGTUPLE 9 Battlestar I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 12 Variety I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Alpine I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 4,200 O
TAGTUPLE 47 aided O
TAGTUPLE 28 Wall I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 12 Motorola I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 24 Whilst O
TAGTUPLE 9 two-run O
TAGTUPLE 40 Gene I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 wary O
TAGTUPLE 24 lexical O
TAGTUPLE 11 Romeo I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Pietro I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 7 slap O
TAGTUPLE 20 c O
TAGTUPLE 148 presidential O
TAGTUPLE 1 Kournikova I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 3 Wilton I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 22 Slavic I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 Evoluon I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 400 I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 11622 he O
TAGTUPLE 34 adherents O
TAGTUPLE 11 Orinoco I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 McGrath I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 8 Genji I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Maxim I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 software I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 10 OpenGL I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Sommers I-PER
TAGTUPLE 15 Dale I-PER
TAGTUPLE 9 reunite O
TAGTUPLE 6 O'Clock I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 appropriated O
TAGTUPLE 5 Annei I-PER
TAGTUPLE 17 Boniface I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 Safeguard I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 50 Coast I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 14 Russians I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 Sera I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 19 Urdu I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 Codasyl I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 8 <d--dd> O
TAGTUPLE 15 Roughly O
TAGTUPLE 36 extinction O
TAGTUPLE 8 Civic I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 provinces I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 64 I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Dominica I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Catiline I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 Osborn I-PER
TAGTUPLE 41 random O
TAGTUPLE 1 nations I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 21 encryption O
TAGTUPLE 64 Iowa I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 trappings O
TAGTUPLE 3 card I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 16 characterization O
TAGTUPLE 7 Aleister I-PER
TAGTUPLE 214 universities O
TAGTUPLE 49 alien O
TAGTUPLE 9 fidelity O
TAGTUPLE 9 Casablanca I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 21 PBS I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 13 Aeolus I-PER
TAGTUPLE 241 methods O
TAGTUPLE 2 Goes I-PER
TAGTUPLE 14 Management I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 13 Kamen I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Pitt I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 11 cloak O
TAGTUPLE 9 Lights I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 Read I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 17 grey O
TAGTUPLE 17 commemorative O
TAGTUPLE 136 onto O
TAGTUPLE 20 Airbus I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 8 Michal I-PER
TAGTUPLE 12 rapes O
TAGTUPLE 11 overland O
TAGTUPLE 5 Sandinistas I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Hammond O
TAGTUPLE 25 Statistik I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 reform I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 12 1757 O
TAGTUPLE 24 Wilder I-PER
TAGTUPLE 54 Democratic I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 sandwich I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Emir I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 143 containing O
TAGTUPLE 39 practicing O
TAGTUPLE 2 orthodox I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 25 fulfill O
TAGTUPLE 6 emissary O
TAGTUPLE 13 cared O
TAGTUPLE 86 magnitude O
TAGTUPLE 5 landlord O
TAGTUPLE 17 encompassing O
TAGTUPLE 32 relate O
TAGTUPLE 2 Candy I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Studios I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 14 Potter I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 123 Each O
TAGTUPLE 24 lending O
TAGTUPLE 7 Direct O
TAGTUPLE 161 White I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 10 panned O
TAGTUPLE 3 Affair I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 chasing O
TAGTUPLE 1 Pyramid O
TAGTUPLE 5 Blanc I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 9 Claudio I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Ogaden I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 7 Linden I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 17 Ramirez I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 Necronomicon I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 21 Swedish I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 10 S-IVB I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 42 Bahá'u'lláh I-PER
TAGTUPLE 3 Scott I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 Westermann I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 Settlements I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 20 jungle O
TAGTUPLE 362 Egypt I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 meager O
TAGTUPLE 473 scientific O
TAGTUPLE 16 egoism O
TAGTUPLE 11 Crane I-PER
TAGTUPLE 79 alternate O
TAGTUPLE 12 Frida I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 94 Christopher I-PER
TAGTUPLE 53 package O
TAGTUPLE 5 peer-reviewed O
TAGTUPLE 20 Suharto I-PER
TAGTUPLE 9 Rupert I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 10080 it O
TAGTUPLE 2 Boston I-PER
TAGTUPLE 3 Carrie I-PER
TAGTUPLE 13 blowing O
TAGTUPLE 5 snap O
TAGTUPLE 1 Hawaii I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 bumbling O
TAGTUPLE 22 Cincinnati I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 176 liberal O
TAGTUPLE 5 1-1 O
TAGTUPLE 12 Helena I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 Bicycle I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 widget I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 47 Ghost I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Gneisenau I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 Mirrors I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 77 Major O
TAGTUPLE 12 bedroom O
TAGTUPLE 9 embargo O
TAGTUPLE 13 insignia O
TAGTUPLE 27 Ariane I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 endorse O
TAGTUPLE 2 Technological O
TAGTUPLE 239 Martin I-PER
TAGTUPLE 50 Motor I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 biomes O
TAGTUPLE 33 bones O
TAGTUPLE 7 organist O
TAGTUPLE 25 transferring O
TAGTUPLE 261 California I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 70 motor O
TAGTUPLE 12 intricate O
TAGTUPLE 3 Health O
TAGTUPLE 7 Hutchins I-PER
TAGTUPLE 43 welcomed O
TAGTUPLE 2 Physical I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 prudent O
TAGTUPLE 11 Putin I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Prophet I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 Admetus I-PER
TAGTUPLE 50 purely O
TAGTUPLE 8 cinema I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 controlled I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 one-dimensional O
TAGTUPLE 4 Jefferson I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 Oedipus I-PER
TAGTUPLE 7 three-day O
TAGTUPLE 5 cathedral I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 19 Cities I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 41 La I-PER
TAGTUPLE 43 73 O
TAGTUPLE 80 practiced O
TAGTUPLE 5 Harum I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 27 Ice-T I-PER
TAGTUPLE 3 summit I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 31 socially O
TAGTUPLE 9 journeyed O
TAGTUPLE 29 Innocent I-PER
TAGTUPLE 15 Pole I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 tunes I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 10 scroll O
TAGTUPLE 8 Treasure I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 3 Conversion O
TAGTUPLE 2 Enterprises I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 Fiction I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 373 fiction O
TAGTUPLE 1 Fighter O
TAGTUPLE 3 Tank I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 18 Hamar I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 119 landed O
TAGTUPLE 11 Magdeburg I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 3 pad I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 doom O
TAGTUPLE 1 AZ I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Nature O
TAGTUPLE 1 Diablo I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 9 IMO I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 7 152 O
TAGTUPLE 1 Warner I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 9 Reclamation I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Autonomy I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Pyramid I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Barking I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 18 kidnapped O
TAGTUPLE 40 Leipzig I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 Element O
TAGTUPLE 4 Mongolian I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 2003 I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 16 pretty O
TAGTUPLE 928 family O
TAGTUPLE 165 hundred O
TAGTUPLE 6 psychoanalytic O
TAGTUPLE 6 impenetrable O
TAGTUPLE 2 Elder I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Reader I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 66 entities O
TAGTUPLE 2 Logic I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 <X-d> O
TAGTUPLE 8 Burj I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 disallowed O
TAGTUPLE 7 buddy O
TAGTUPLE 1 Branch I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 9 Cluny I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 Rashomon I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 Maore I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 8 2017 O
TAGTUPLE 4 Uruguay I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Gama I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 4 Hadassah I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 urban I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Rancho I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 8 druids O
TAGTUPLE 31 Hobbes I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 80s I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 404 O
TAGTUPLE 90 pilots O
TAGTUPLE 28 Mick I-PER
TAGTUPLE 87 promised O
TAGTUPLE 8 Staff I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 Fields I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 23 oversight O
TAGTUPLE 1 Short I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 7 bleak O
TAGTUPLE 1 </x-x(> O
TAGTUPLE 9 Rugby I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 10 geared O
TAGTUPLE 15 106 O
TAGTUPLE 13 aspirations O
TAGTUPLE 7 Nile I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 62 MLB I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 RAM I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 159 minister O
TAGTUPLE 5 Rage I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 TeX I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 9 south-western O
TAGTUPLE 8 Kyrenia I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 Norway I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 1635 O
TAGTUPLE 5 Ainslie I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 13 saxophonist O
TAGTUPLE 21 XVI I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Canberra I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 11 breakout O
TAGTUPLE 25 Badan I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 8 ACT I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 à I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 cognomen O
TAGTUPLE 27 horn O
TAGTUPLE 1 Londonderry I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 neural O
TAGTUPLE 9 <d.> O
TAGTUPLE 23 Sumatra I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 3270 O
TAGTUPLE 1 Aliyev I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 7 Information O
TAGTUPLE 75 onwards O
TAGTUPLE 11 di I-PER
TAGTUPLE 22 All-Star O
TAGTUPLE 13 scarcely O
TAGTUPLE 5 expandable O
TAGTUPLE 25 disguised O
TAGTUPLE 5 Lodger I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 Rogers I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 68 battleships O
TAGTUPLE 2 Annie I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 Miriam I-PER
TAGTUPLE 216 contrast O
TAGTUPLE 31 strained O
TAGTUPLE 2 Pravda I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 1565 O
TAGTUPLE 19 Supreme I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 infrequently O
TAGTUPLE 25 Oklahoma I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 2.x O
TAGTUPLE 6 mammal O
TAGTUPLE 394 argued O
TAGTUPLE 226 advanced O
TAGTUPLE 90 Salvador I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 Tank O
TAGTUPLE 2 Active I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 63 Wayne I-PER
TAGTUPLE 112 goddess O
TAGTUPLE 1 Dig I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 discrepancies O
TAGTUPLE 170 1947 O
TAGTUPLE 5 Dresden I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 9 hierarchies O
TAGTUPLE 2 Macleod I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 7 education I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 194 Jackson I-PER
TAGTUPLE 20 Dogs I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 35 stops O
TAGTUPLE 1 Harlan I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 4 Team O
TAGTUPLE 10 Ferrol I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 14 volleyball O
TAGTUPLE 1 Reis I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 Californians I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 11 frescoes O
TAGTUPLE 8 plateau I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 declination O
TAGTUPLE 13 testament O
TAGTUPLE 44 harm O
TAGTUPLE 70 bomber O
TAGTUPLE 27 Barcelona I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Test O
TAGTUPLE 2 Low O
TAGTUPLE 2 1st I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Azad I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Vigo I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 9 Letterman I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 12 Mahabharata I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 archipelago I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 4 Lorentz I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 Legion I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 294 immediately O
TAGTUPLE 42 BSA I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 34 unofficial O
TAGTUPLE 5 Metropolitan I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 13 warship O
TAGTUPLE 10 <Xxdxx> I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 15 mater O
TAGTUPLE 67 Hans I-PER
TAGTUPLE 32 subdivided O
TAGTUPLE 15 calcium O
TAGTUPLE 9 Edvard I-PER
TAGTUPLE 41 Football I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 Tenggara I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 magnum O
TAGTUPLE 122 violent O
TAGTUPLE 4 Planned I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 Tram I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 144 diverse O
TAGTUPLE 6 Albornoz I-PER
TAGTUPLE 365 previously O
TAGTUPLE 5 V-1 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 22 Ramsey I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 Piran I-PER
TAGTUPLE 9 frustrating O
TAGTUPLE 1 cellular I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 3 Variations I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Rams I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 CL I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 10 Some I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 70 discoveries O
TAGTUPLE 9 center-left O
TAGTUPLE 1 promise I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 11 anybody O
TAGTUPLE 5 Steffi I-PER
TAGTUPLE 3 Portugal I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 19 Draft I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 Official O
TAGTUPLE 8 resorted O
TAGTUPLE 236 levels O
TAGTUPLE 7 confuse O
TAGTUPLE 591 level O
TAGTUPLE 58 Sony I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 20 Harbor I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 15 humankind O
TAGTUPLE 13 exam O
TAGTUPLE 43 ideology O
TAGTUPLE 31 precision O
TAGTUPLE 23 owed O
TAGTUPLE 6 Marsyas I-PER
TAGTUPLE 32 hanging O
TAGTUPLE 6 conversely O
TAGTUPLE 6 fairies O
TAGTUPLE 1 Edward I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 14 Succession I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 workstation O
TAGTUPLE 2 Santa I-PER
TAGTUPLE 31 martial O
TAGTUPLE 4 Camelot I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 ironclad O
TAGTUPLE 12 torpedoes O
TAGTUPLE 18 Nineteen I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 9 Buridan I-PER
TAGTUPLE 23 90s O
TAGTUPLE 2 Daley I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 natively O
TAGTUPLE 3 Forward I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 111 annually O
TAGTUPLE 77 Romans I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Lulu I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 Boys O
TAGTUPLE 7 1979 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 252 nine O
TAGTUPLE 19 Tang I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 alkaline O
TAGTUPLE 5 promotions O
TAGTUPLE 14 mayors O
TAGTUPLE 64 confusion O
TAGTUPLE 12 diagram O
TAGTUPLE 2 did I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 18 doubtful O
TAGTUPLE 17 fitting O
TAGTUPLE 8 sadness O
TAGTUPLE 1 Cruise I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 128 trying O
TAGTUPLE 21 plutonium O
TAGTUPLE 8 courted O
TAGTUPLE 4 intern O
TAGTUPLE 43 Indies I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 artistry O
TAGTUPLE 6 pirates I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 16 dislike O
TAGTUPLE 65 fresh O
TAGTUPLE 17 Inspired O
TAGTUPLE 8 inmate O
TAGTUPLE 20 175 O
TAGTUPLE 1 Legends I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 13 professions O
TAGTUPLE 18 goats O
TAGTUPLE 31 Die I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 3 ABC I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Baylor I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 thoughtful O
TAGTUPLE 9 Atlanta I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 Chilean I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 spy I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 18 recorder O
TAGTUPLE 7 Fighter I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 Savage I-PER
TAGTUPLE 73 pope O
TAGTUPLE 19 extract O
TAGTUPLE 9 rhyming O
TAGTUPLE 2 Swedish O
TAGTUPLE 5 plebeians O
TAGTUPLE 6 Niobe I-PER
TAGTUPLE 24 ballistic O
TAGTUPLE 3 Kimmel I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 10 murderer O
TAGTUPLE 19 pointers O
TAGTUPLE 24 renewal O
TAGTUPLE 2 impact I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 8 Eridu I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 captured I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 35 Grande I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 886 various O
TAGTUPLE 3 Horse O
TAGTUPLE 3 Ravi I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 boy I-PER
TAGTUPLE 11 NSDAP I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 12 1559 O
TAGTUPLE 1 Thorn I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 9 Clock I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 25 securing O
TAGTUPLE 5 Aneurin I-PER
TAGTUPLE 37 Abner I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 14 contraction O
TAGTUPLE 15 Turks I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 566 2000 O
TAGTUPLE 5 Elders I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 fuel I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 13 exiles O
TAGTUPLE 8 List I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 <x'XxX> I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 onstage O
TAGTUPLE 16 Sound I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 65 opportunities O
TAGTUPLE 1 Church O
TAGTUPLE 5 exploratory O
TAGTUPLE 1 map I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Cocos I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 36 contributor O
TAGTUPLE 8 1756 O
TAGTUPLE 11 aerodynamics O
TAGTUPLE 5 clockwise O
TAGTUPLE 6 conscripts O
TAGTUPLE 1 life I-PER
TAGTUPLE 13 Father I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 271 1969 O
TAGTUPLE 1 Montaigne I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 9 Kent I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 cross-shaped O
TAGTUPLE 4 Wet I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 7 Lepida I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 project I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 41 d'Ivoire I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 9 Everett I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 Hind I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 cruises O
TAGTUPLE 6 triumvirate O
TAGTUPLE 14 Fletcher I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 flavors O
TAGTUPLE 11 Miss I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 memorably O
TAGTUPLE 3 Commercial I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 balked O
TAGTUPLE 1 Market O
TAGTUPLE 2 Acton I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 55 shall O
TAGTUPLE 1 fictional I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 15 warn O
TAGTUPLE 45 depicting O
TAGTUPLE 2 revival I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 sprite O
TAGTUPLE 1 Governments I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 Albi I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 124 hosts O
TAGTUPLE 45 Apart O
TAGTUPLE 6 fills O
TAGTUPLE 128 ceremony O
TAGTUPLE 2 Bridge O
TAGTUPLE 5 Kortrijk I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 4 704 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 12 slept O
TAGTUPLE 5 Actium I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 19 discharge O
TAGTUPLE 11 FRG I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Bass I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 10 Apollos I-PER
TAGTUPLE 27 assumes O
TAGTUPLE 1 Former I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 84 Conan I-PER
TAGTUPLE 13 Lacan I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 nonexistent O
TAGTUPLE 16 Camelot I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 133 1943 O
TAGTUPLE 61 Wikipedia I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 franchise I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Luxembourg I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 34 weekend O
TAGTUPLE 7 anti-nuclear O
TAGTUPLE 38 terminology O
TAGTUPLE 9 songwriters O
TAGTUPLE 11 Celilo I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 11 tentatively O
TAGTUPLE 6 Unknown O
TAGTUPLE 5 Srebrenica I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 15 trait O
TAGTUPLE 215 fought O
TAGTUPLE 17 One I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2426 up O
TAGTUPLE 8 Nadu I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 Contemporary I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 9 olives O
TAGTUPLE 5 broadest O
TAGTUPLE 1 Publishing I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 16 Eros I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 colleges I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Weyl I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 <d,d> O
TAGTUPLE 5 IFAB I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 12 dormant O
TAGTUPLE 15 850 O
TAGTUPLE 1 Westminster I-PER
TAGTUPLE 18 menu O
TAGTUPLE 5 Dehumanizer I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Bavarian I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 155 Jerusalem I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 Teutoburg I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 11 Hefner I-PER
TAGTUPLE 115 agency O
TAGTUPLE 2 Corpse I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Cumberland I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 4 Period I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 online I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 12 mitigate O
TAGTUPLE 35 induction O
TAGTUPLE 6 bulb O
TAGTUPLE 3 Steam I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 starkly O
TAGTUPLE 5 generalship O
TAGTUPLE 62 linking O
TAGTUPLE 24 lineage O
TAGTUPLE 1 Wisdom I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Valencia I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 No. I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 9 Show I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 13 peripheral O
TAGTUPLE 13 hijacked O
TAGTUPLE 6 1350 O
TAGTUPLE 7 subduction O
TAGTUPLE 2 headquarters I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 28 Books I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Complete I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 89 ban O
TAGTUPLE 1 Wichita I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 36 AGP I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Woodward I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 12 Harmony I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 11 G8 I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 ASIMO I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Astoria I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 19 Sebastian I-PER
TAGTUPLE 102 singles O
TAGTUPLE 1 seven I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 Mercian I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 Herzegovina I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 3 Burlington I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Bellamy I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 Argyll I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 127 <XXX> I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Dynasty I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 orally O
TAGTUPLE 2 democracy I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Violet I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 17 1400 O
TAGTUPLE 6 Jeong-eum I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 18 orthodoxy O
TAGTUPLE 2 <Xx-.Xx.> I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 3 Progressive I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 Damin I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Bon I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 Chain I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 42 Stuart I-PER
TAGTUPLE 411 brother O
TAGTUPLE 5 whim O
TAGTUPLE 21 Engineers I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 4 Sex I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 41 Helen I-PER
TAGTUPLE 82 33 O
TAGTUPLE 1 governance I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 7 Six I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 19 intersection O
TAGTUPLE 19 Dalton I-PER
TAGTUPLE 19 Tajikistan I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 3 Goodwin I-PER
TAGTUPLE 12 relocation O
TAGTUPLE 3 Fawcett I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Sybil I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 109 merged O
TAGTUPLE 18 fare O
TAGTUPLE 6 Servius I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Cedar I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 9 psyche O
TAGTUPLE 8 bowls O
TAGTUPLE 1 1829 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 29 12,000 O
TAGTUPLE 10 Douglas I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Tull I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 sued I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 <Xx.d> I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 26 Contest I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 14 decrees O
TAGTUPLE 14 co-starring O
TAGTUPLE 8 M4 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 3 70s I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 9 steals O
TAGTUPLE 1 Call I-PER
TAGTUPLE 85 eyes O
TAGTUPLE 7 inhuman O
TAGTUPLE 8 branching O
TAGTUPLE 87 Honda I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 13 displacement O
TAGTUPLE 6 Finney I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 estimated I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 <x.dx> O
TAGTUPLE 34 96 O
TAGTUPLE 1 adopted I-PER
TAGTUPLE 26 postulated O
TAGTUPLE 6 immoral O
TAGTUPLE 10 consulate O
TAGTUPLE 1 Esther I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 10 boar O
TAGTUPLE 8 viewpoints O
TAGTUPLE 1 41 I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 24 Byron I-PER
TAGTUPLE 7 Olympics I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 7 headers O
TAGTUPLE 8 interdiction O
TAGTUPLE 1 NBC O
TAGTUPLE 513 BC O
TAGTUPLE 245 ruled O
TAGTUPLE 3 Mountains I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 27 equilibrium O
TAGTUPLE 6 forcefully O
TAGTUPLE 25 paradox O
TAGTUPLE 15 Anglia I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 1919 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 Krogstad I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Hazael I-PER
TAGTUPLE 10 chronicle O
TAGTUPLE 11 practise O
TAGTUPLE 22 Brother I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 principles I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Cheltenham I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 Swiss I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 16 Phoenix I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 Cruijff I-PER
TAGTUPLE 25 AI O
TAGTUPLE 1 Petrarch I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 147 lowest O
TAGTUPLE 8 fateful O
TAGTUPLE 1 Avery I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 Alarcón I-PER
TAGTUPLE 23 hectares O
TAGTUPLE 5 fricatives O
TAGTUPLE 5 conceding O
TAGTUPLE 4 Barr I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 87 inland O
TAGTUPLE 8 Bleak I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 operetta I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 Bemba I-PER
TAGTUPLE 17 honesty O
TAGTUPLE 6 pagans O
TAGTUPLE 5 devising O
TAGTUPLE 6 nocturnal O
TAGTUPLE 8 Crossing I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 79 leagues O
TAGTUPLE 173 poetry O
TAGTUPLE 9 222 O
TAGTUPLE 271 shown O
TAGTUPLE 36 Cleese I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 Setting I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 barracks I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 Hydra I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 Rank I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 16 144 O
TAGTUPLE 17 Crowded I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 155 apparently O
TAGTUPLE 6 Zia I-PER
TAGTUPLE 88 Octavian I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 231 O
TAGTUPLE 29 enterprises O
TAGTUPLE 12 Abelard I-PER
TAGTUPLE 10 Spike I-PER
TAGTUPLE 15 idol O
TAGTUPLE 5 bureaus O
TAGTUPLE 200 St. I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 36 proponents O
TAGTUPLE 40 reminiscent O
TAGTUPLE 3 Workers I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 4 <Xx.Xxx> I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 4 objects I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Samuel I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 8 Children O
TAGTUPLE 132 notion O
TAGTUPLE 31 flexible O
TAGTUPLE 37 sketches O
TAGTUPLE 4 Gilbert I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Range I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 Jupiter I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Correspondence O
TAGTUPLE 2 Mafia I-PER
TAGTUPLE 129 Gaza I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 18 stabbed O
TAGTUPLE 5 sweeps O
TAGTUPLE 10 Hitler I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Andersen I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 284 student O
TAGTUPLE 8 revolt I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Rankin I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 90 populous O
TAGTUPLE 4 Tea I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 9 Desilu I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 <dxd^> O
TAGTUPLE 5 financier O
TAGTUPLE 31 Spanish I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 25 helium O
TAGTUPLE 46 Security I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 scandalous O
TAGTUPLE 2 Evans I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 261 Book I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 House I-PER
TAGTUPLE 12 lamented O
TAGTUPLE 11 physique O
TAGTUPLE 94 bishop O
TAGTUPLE 1 Cardinals O
TAGTUPLE 3 Pollard I-PER
TAGTUPLE 44 demanding O
TAGTUPLE 6 rebuffed O
TAGTUPLE 13 Papers I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Kettering I-PER
TAGTUPLE 186 male O
TAGTUPLE 10 turbocharged O
TAGTUPLE 3 President I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 17 primordial O
TAGTUPLE 2 design I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 12 frequented O
TAGTUPLE 1 Fur I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 13 harshly O
TAGTUPLE 8 projective O
TAGTUPLE 17 fathered O
TAGTUPLE 149 association O
TAGTUPLE 6 gramophone O
TAGTUPLE 44 directions O
TAGTUPLE 6 paddle O
TAGTUPLE 66 Eugene I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 9 praetor O
TAGTUPLE 5 InterBase I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 Compostela I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 33 occupying O
TAGTUPLE 11 Northwest I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 36 volunteer O
TAGTUPLE 74 equally O
TAGTUPLE 1 flag I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 kindly O
TAGTUPLE 8 dispensed O
TAGTUPLE 7 confessions O
TAGTUPLE 5 IERS I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 690 O
TAGTUPLE 10 donate O
TAGTUPLE 21 Albert I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 10 television I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 21 Parliament O
TAGTUPLE 1 Belgium I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 Salazar I-PER
TAGTUPLE 59 contracts O
TAGTUPLE 2 25 I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 15 reefs O
TAGTUPLE 5 judgements O
TAGTUPLE 10 glue O
TAGTUPLE 3 feminists I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Theo I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 Col. O
TAGTUPLE 145 request O
TAGTUPLE 9 abridged O
TAGTUPLE 17 Southern I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Espoo I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 9 Whitney I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Ecclesiastical I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Mass I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Armstrong I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 retold O
TAGTUPLE 11 radiant O
TAGTUPLE 6 camouflage O
TAGTUPLE 1 Brod I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 7 256-bit O
TAGTUPLE 5 county I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 10 facade O
TAGTUPLE 30 Historians O
TAGTUPLE 6 afield O
TAGTUPLE 137 height O
TAGTUPLE 10 Vieira I-PER
TAGTUPLE 7 urges O
TAGTUPLE 1 Schultz I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Dakota I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 173 heard O
TAGTUPLE 309 therefore O
TAGTUPLE 8 400 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 British I-PER
TAGTUPLE 96 About O
TAGTUPLE 34 CN I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 aerosols O
TAGTUPLE 114 centers O
TAGTUPLE 17 Around I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 modularity O
TAGTUPLE 3 Written I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 21 do I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2056 well O
TAGTUPLE 8 Ada I-PER
TAGTUPLE 24 academy O
TAGTUPLE 32 wherein O
TAGTUPLE 10 campus I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 calculator I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 14 bureaucratic O
TAGTUPLE 18 betrayed O
TAGTUPLE 258 Ruth I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 Sara I-PER
TAGTUPLE 15 Elway I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 Houses I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 63 fourteen O
TAGTUPLE 4 Chemical O
TAGTUPLE 1 Boat I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Plant I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Institut I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 Rain I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Melinda I-PER
TAGTUPLE 22 Toyota I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 136 establishment O
TAGTUPLE 60 plains O
TAGTUPLE 1 supplier I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Valle I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 <X-Xdx> I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 58 structural O
TAGTUPLE 91 disputed O
TAGTUPLE 2 Said I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 3585 years O
TAGTUPLE 40 Ross I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 meadows O
TAGTUPLE 5 Guam I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Five I-PER
TAGTUPLE 23 intensified O
TAGTUPLE 5 patrician O
TAGTUPLE 38 confirmation O
TAGTUPLE 2 soundtrack I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 Tanganyika I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 7 Slovak I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 sensing O
TAGTUPLE 6 clique O
TAGTUPLE 35 Generally O
TAGTUPLE 28 Hoffer I-PER
TAGTUPLE 7 begs O
TAGTUPLE 86 Canadian I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Olympic I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 Merthyr I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 37 papal O
TAGTUPLE 7 Thurman I-PER
TAGTUPLE 3 Italy O
TAGTUPLE 132 unusual O
TAGTUPLE 6 expanse O
TAGTUPLE 42 outer O
TAGTUPLE 7 Constantina I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 Bette I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Nemean I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Ogaden I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 Amanda I-PER
TAGTUPLE 18 Canberra I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Malaysian O
TAGTUPLE 1 Palestrina I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 1,000 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Goya I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 24 partnerships O
TAGTUPLE 10 deuterium O
TAGTUPLE 8 modestly O
TAGTUPLE 4 Basquiat I-PER
TAGTUPLE 37 ensemble O
TAGTUPLE 139 Adams I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Magnus I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 42 B-2 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 declension O
TAGTUPLE 3 Inn I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 voicing O
TAGTUPLE 75 Doom I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 9 receipts O
TAGTUPLE 15 dhimmis O
TAGTUPLE 1 Monetary O
TAGTUPLE 71 rivalry O
TAGTUPLE 34 Tommy I-PER
TAGTUPLE 70 Frankish I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 102 Tiberius I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Constituent I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 <~ddd> O
TAGTUPLE 21 eruptions O
TAGTUPLE 8 Haworth I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 12 compounded O
TAGTUPLE 21 satisfaction O
TAGTUPLE 2 Beta I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 21 Hewlett-Packard I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 377 ancient O
TAGTUPLE 1 ? I-PER
TAGTUPLE 4 Belarus I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 30 rotating O
TAGTUPLE 6 aeronautics O
TAGTUPLE 41 Zubaydah I-PER
TAGTUPLE 4 prism O
TAGTUPLE 5 mentality O
TAGTUPLE 39 moments O
TAGTUPLE 1 Armstrong I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 7 horizontally O
TAGTUPLE 334 refer O
TAGTUPLE 50 nationalist O
TAGTUPLE 5 proletariat O
TAGTUPLE 4 Chi I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Becket I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 22 backdrop O
TAGTUPLE 1 Hunt O
TAGTUPLE 2 Eureka I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 7 motivating O
TAGTUPLE 5 JetBlue I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 7 XT I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 125 Israeli I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 <xx/:dd> O
TAGTUPLE 16 scouting O
TAGTUPLE 8 Brownlow I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 157 kilometers O
TAGTUPLE 926 United I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 3 Hampton I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 191 O
TAGTUPLE 1 centers I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 69 peninsula O
TAGTUPLE 4 Saeed I-PER
TAGTUPLE 39 weakness O
TAGTUPLE 32 Gulf I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 oust O
TAGTUPLE 53 anywhere O
TAGTUPLE 79 expand O
TAGTUPLE 84 acceptance O
TAGTUPLE 5 nozzle O
TAGTUPLE 12 upbringing O
TAGTUPLE 107 Cameroon I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 8 nominees O
TAGTUPLE 71 French I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 65 noir O
TAGTUPLE 1 Edgar I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 myth I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 Demerara I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 enzymes O
TAGTUPLE 10 usefulness O
TAGTUPLE 5 curiosities O
TAGTUPLE 7 N.M. I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 Strike I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 366 separate O
TAGTUPLE 2 Merseyside I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Stark I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 9 Whitehead I-PER
TAGTUPLE 42 compilers O
TAGTUPLE 10 Adler I-PER
TAGTUPLE 3 colonial I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 detention I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 Empress I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 Imamura I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 Dearborn I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 161 Unlike O
TAGTUPLE 4 report I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 latterly O
TAGTUPLE 6 Caves I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 Tukey I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Jewish O
TAGTUPLE 6 oscillation O
TAGTUPLE 8 DiMaggio I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 Yates I-PER
TAGTUPLE 3 O'Connell I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 19 asylum O
TAGTUPLE 12 1769 O
TAGTUPLE 1 homosexuality I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 7 Handbook I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 Athenaeus I-PER
TAGTUPLE 4 Hanoi I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Suburban O
TAGTUPLE 5 zoological O
TAGTUPLE 2 cm I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 Smeaton I-PER
TAGTUPLE 34 Madrid I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 Waffen-SS I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 9 RAF I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 4 Belize I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 27 sank O
TAGTUPLE 11 Towers I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 152 images O
TAGTUPLE 7 1523 O
TAGTUPLE 18 chaotic O
TAGTUPLE 106 plain O
TAGTUPLE 6 Aquarius I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 hotel I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 7 EFnet I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 45 remarks O
TAGTUPLE 4 Durrell I-PER
TAGTUPLE 17 miniseries O
TAGTUPLE 5 Yitzhak I-PER
TAGTUPLE 56 Court I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 3 Larkin I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 4 Waco I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 30 Lara I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Erasmus I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 23 interviewed O
TAGTUPLE 6 maidens O
TAGTUPLE 12 Rainfall O
TAGTUPLE 5 app O
TAGTUPLE 5 Unitas I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 fuelled O
TAGTUPLE 266 completely O
TAGTUPLE 6 repaid O
TAGTUPLE 15 ninety O
TAGTUPLE 10 LISP I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Filipino I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 36 anonymous O
TAGTUPLE 1 fighters I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 diversifying O
TAGTUPLE 1 Silent I-PER
TAGTUPLE 60 emperors O
TAGTUPLE 5 Carey I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Hong I-PER
TAGTUPLE 409 movie O
TAGTUPLE 6 fiefs O
TAGTUPLE 10 enjoyment O
TAGTUPLE 5 Politics O
TAGTUPLE 83 pioneered O
TAGTUPLE 135 southwest O
TAGTUPLE 11 loaned O
TAGTUPLE 2 Mutina I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 27 fascinated O
TAGTUPLE 32 Civilization I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 339 stage O
TAGTUPLE 7 Hamburg I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 41 da I-PER
TAGTUPLE 14 literate O
TAGTUPLE 33 Sometimes O
TAGTUPLE 155 Pacific I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 11 incremental O
TAGTUPLE 8 reversible O
TAGTUPLE 4 2000 I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 voltage O
TAGTUPLE 11 warlords O
TAGTUPLE 224 organizations O
TAGTUPLE 7 chefs O
TAGTUPLE 3909 all O
TAGTUPLE 87 i O
TAGTUPLE 7 upload O
TAGTUPLE 1 dualism I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Telephone I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Freddie I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Your I-PER
TAGTUPLE 7 Gettysburg I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 Lonely I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 12 alternatively O
TAGTUPLE 1 Place I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 Applesoft I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Laboratory I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 17 theft O
TAGTUPLE 8 jockey O
TAGTUPLE 5 älv I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 82 cabinet O
TAGTUPLE 5 easiest O
TAGTUPLE 5 Bonanza I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 10 romances O
TAGTUPLE 1 Durrell I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 17 Penh I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 11 scholarships O
TAGTUPLE 3 Unity I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 77 comments O
TAGTUPLE 32 Rick I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 plating O
TAGTUPLE 55 1865 O
TAGTUPLE 7 1439 O
TAGTUPLE 3 49th I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Clampetts I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 265 O
TAGTUPLE 8 staircase O
TAGTUPLE 18 Hong I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 15 Faroe I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 3 Appalachian I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 73 suggestion O
TAGTUPLE 2 Deimos I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 Aurora I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 Manx I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 steering O
TAGTUPLE 1 Expedition I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 Amerigo I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Summer I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 But I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 14 Mirror I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 specialising O
TAGTUPLE 5 ii O
TAGTUPLE 25 Buddy I-PER
TAGTUPLE 13 subgenre O
TAGTUPLE 2 Instrument I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 325 O
TAGTUPLE 10 30s O
TAGTUPLE 41 ancestry O
TAGTUPLE 26 sake O
TAGTUPLE 2 Everyone I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 Sister I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 10 Planet I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Rose O
TAGTUPLE 135 Speer I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 Stephen I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 3099 city O
TAGTUPLE 243 older O
TAGTUPLE 41 favourite O
TAGTUPLE 25 Gregor I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 architecture I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 24 lined O
TAGTUPLE 5 nutrients O
TAGTUPLE 2 -- I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 Nakhchivan I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 16 violated O
TAGTUPLE 1 1502 I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 10 Proposal I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Giants I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1902 government O
TAGTUPLE 53 emergence O
TAGTUPLE 24 automotive O
TAGTUPLE 13 1515 O
TAGTUPLE 4 Amateur I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 1190 O
TAGTUPLE 3 mainframes I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 Nobel I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 11 outfit O
TAGTUPLE 11 <x'xx> I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 26 contingent O
TAGTUPLE 6 Caledonia I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 8 cooked O
TAGTUPLE 91 Microsoft I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 ) I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 itinerant O
TAGTUPLE 10 mass-produced O
TAGTUPLE 12 m² O
TAGTUPLE 25 flash O
TAGTUPLE 1 subgenre I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Pollock I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Abdullah I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 Unity O
TAGTUPLE 5 slice O
TAGTUPLE 5 Aberdour I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 9 lieu O
TAGTUPLE 1 doll I-PER
TAGTUPLE 20 IV I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 43 unrest O
TAGTUPLE 92 obtain O
TAGTUPLE 76 Chief O
TAGTUPLE 11 <xx-xd> O
TAGTUPLE 13 vegetable O
TAGTUPLE 10 parachute O
TAGTUPLE 1 <d/dd> I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 10 Scientists O
TAGTUPLE 58 animation O
TAGTUPLE 644 20 O
TAGTUPLE 5 prolifically O
TAGTUPLE 5 nous O
TAGTUPLE 6 Beauvoir I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 1695 O
TAGTUPLE 36 quote O
TAGTUPLE 37 infant O
TAGTUPLE 3 GP I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Cádiz I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 4 Rockefeller I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 98 false O
TAGTUPLE 468 might O
TAGTUPLE 5 Amid O
TAGTUPLE 77 print O
TAGTUPLE 1 Crooked I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 20 burst O
TAGTUPLE 1 Nick I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 8 expiration O
TAGTUPLE 46 desired O
TAGTUPLE 8 Nicaraguan I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Sputnik I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Lombardi O
TAGTUPLE 207 200 O
TAGTUPLE 1 Corsican I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 12 Chamber I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 7 Binet I-PER
TAGTUPLE 282 stars O
TAGTUPLE 25 rejects O
TAGTUPLE 5 Crimson I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 building I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 Boulder I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 7 Pappas I-PER
TAGTUPLE 14 owe O
TAGTUPLE 15 Barbuda I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Rey I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 22 bodily O
TAGTUPLE 29 hiatus O
TAGTUPLE 5 seeded O
TAGTUPLE 22 deserted O
TAGTUPLE 1 Roses I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 3 C I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 14 Seeger I-PER
TAGTUPLE 9 Oklahoma I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 triangle I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 scanner O
TAGTUPLE 8 shouting O
TAGTUPLE 2 Athens I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 was I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 22 reconstructed O
TAGTUPLE 12 W3C I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 10 bend O
TAGTUPLE 13 Kalinga I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 14 Albany I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 boot I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 11 resultant O
TAGTUPLE 15 stark O
TAGTUPLE 12 relativistic O
TAGTUPLE 11 Barbarossa I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 poignant O
TAGTUPLE 11 informs O
TAGTUPLE 3 Boulton I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 Guru I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 162 management O
TAGTUPLE 6 Fat I-PER
TAGTUPLE 27 Béla I-PER
TAGTUPLE 33 livestock O
TAGTUPLE 3 Vale I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 14 mid-1960s O
TAGTUPLE 6 Fortress I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 18 alignment O
TAGTUPLE 37 Bartók I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 troupes O
TAGTUPLE 5 Recovery I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Maltese I-PER
TAGTUPLE 109 Elgar I-PER
TAGTUPLE 10 prompt O
TAGTUPLE 6 Li I-PER
TAGTUPLE 11 presidential I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 10 Sarawak I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 8 systemic O
TAGTUPLE 2 11th I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 123 establishing O
TAGTUPLE 3 Flower I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 Watergate I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 964 According O
TAGTUPLE 30 pressed O
TAGTUPLE 16 resume O
TAGTUPLE 21 recruit O
TAGTUPLE 24 Little I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 15 <XX/XX> I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 Stibitz I-PER
TAGTUPLE 38 helicopter O
TAGTUPLE 4 Kursk I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 9 intertwined O
TAGTUPLE 30 <Xxx> O
TAGTUPLE 2 September I-PER
TAGTUPLE 7 Kaliningrad I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 10 overhaul O
TAGTUPLE 5 1770s O
TAGTUPLE 10 Sandra I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Conservatives O
TAGTUPLE 10 Philippe I-PER
TAGTUPLE 56 1889 O
TAGTUPLE 108 forming O
TAGTUPLE 23 coca O
TAGTUPLE 4 … I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Marble O
TAGTUPLE 4 Million I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 20 Sacramento I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 G. I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Saarinen I-PER
TAGTUPLE 22 El I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 14 Mayhem I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 15 Schoenberg I-PER
TAGTUPLE 52 fortune O
TAGTUPLE 1 Dam I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 diminish O
TAGTUPLE 3 Moro I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 effect I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 38 marking O
TAGTUPLE 1 Mason O
TAGTUPLE 59 Arkansas I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 7 spectacularly O
TAGTUPLE 2 Manu I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 <ddd*> O
TAGTUPLE 12 Bin I-PER
TAGTUPLE 7 Harmonization I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 Relay I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 153 respect O
TAGTUPLE 5 Tenant I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 4 dissolution I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 Renaissance I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 35 regards O
TAGTUPLE 6 Athens I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 37 long-time O
TAGTUPLE 19 Oregon I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 8 1563 O
TAGTUPLE 1 Both I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 deception O
TAGTUPLE 82 cinema O
TAGTUPLE 6 gunships O
TAGTUPLE 3 <xx-/dxd> O
TAGTUPLE 1 Tours O
TAGTUPLE 36 Methodist I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 war I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 33 saving O
TAGTUPLE 13 Dara I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 Buster I-PER
TAGTUPLE 153 1954 O
TAGTUPLE 7 Lucretius I-PER
TAGTUPLE 101 supposed O
TAGTUPLE 1 circumcision I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 18 insist O
TAGTUPLE 5 belligerent O
TAGTUPLE 6 Division I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 19 profoundly O
TAGTUPLE 2 Sant I-PER
TAGTUPLE 17 <dd.dx> O
TAGTUPLE 6 retrieval O
TAGTUPLE 6 Rawlinson I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 penis O
TAGTUPLE 23 biodiversity O
TAGTUPLE 1 PHP O
TAGTUPLE 9 Mont I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Naturalis I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 61 UEFA I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 Durham I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 waterway I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 8 patriotism O
TAGTUPLE 5 Spy I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 indiscriminate O
TAGTUPLE 55 junior O
TAGTUPLE 12 socialists O
TAGTUPLE 2 Poverty O
TAGTUPLE 7 Ice I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 16 semi-final O
TAGTUPLE 2 Romulus I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 32 boarding O
TAGTUPLE 18 Already O
TAGTUPLE 13 Apostle I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 mastering O
TAGTUPLE 1 variants I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 66 AFC I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 51 wireless O
TAGTUPLE 7 Actaeon I-PER
TAGTUPLE 2 Jonathan I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 219 instance O
TAGTUPLE 14 César I-PER
TAGTUPLE 4 Morris I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 Shoeless I-PER
TAGTUPLE 26 averages O
TAGTUPLE 2 <X> O
TAGTUPLE 6 Rumelia I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 116 factory O
TAGTUPLE 6 Bhai I-PER
TAGTUPLE 133 stood O
TAGTUPLE 9 Fairbanks I-PER
TAGTUPLE 34 wait O
TAGTUPLE 5 HTTP/1.0 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 44 undertaken O
TAGTUPLE 28 drag O
TAGTUPLE 1 pm I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 3 <X-XX> I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 19 relying O
TAGTUPLE 1 Tower I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 56 automatically O
TAGTUPLE 136 stone O
TAGTUPLE 1 550 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 88 coverage O
TAGTUPLE 45 shop O
TAGTUPLE 42 attractive O
TAGTUPLE 2 Enola I-PER
TAGTUPLE 4 revolutionary I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 17 <d/dd> O
TAGTUPLE 10 enlist O
TAGTUPLE 26 Canterbury O
TAGTUPLE 1 Hanukkah O
TAGTUPLE 5 Akihabara I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 9 Synod I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Relay I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 7 Münster I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 3 mine I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 5 aunts O
TAGTUPLE 5 utilised O
TAGTUPLE 1 <Xd-/XX> I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Chad I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 10 verification O
TAGTUPLE 8 standardised O
TAGTUPLE 9 IMAP O
TAGTUPLE 2 regime I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 8 Rickey I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 trumpeter O
TAGTUPLE 1 one I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 whipped O
TAGTUPLE 6 Hannes I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Self O
TAGTUPLE 5 etiological O
TAGTUPLE 25 alike O
TAGTUPLE 14 stuff O
TAGTUPLE 9 slay O
TAGTUPLE 124 participated O
TAGTUPLE 5 Tender I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 due I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 outpaced O
TAGTUPLE 42 Knight I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 6 chickens O
TAGTUPLE 7 B.C. O
TAGTUPLE 4 Syrian I-PER
TAGTUPLE 48 2006 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Westinghouse I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 collapse I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 27 Cross I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 351 create O
TAGTUPLE 1 Engine I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 cartels O
TAGTUPLE 31 pupils O
TAGTUPLE 59 belong O
TAGTUPLE 71 = O
TAGTUPLE 1 Monica I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Damon I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 fearful O
TAGTUPLE 1 Affairs I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Daria I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 biting O
TAGTUPLE 14 Warrior I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 <XX+X> I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Southwest O
TAGTUPLE 3 Electronics I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 Europe O
TAGTUPLE 6 motors O
TAGTUPLE 1 Bennett I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 26 1783 O
TAGTUPLE 9 profitability O
TAGTUPLE 12 reproduce O
TAGTUPLE 6 Ofcom I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 president I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 8 branched O
TAGTUPLE 1 <=xxx> O
TAGTUPLE 13 Supporting I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 southerly O
TAGTUPLE 1 Merton I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 6 pandemic O
TAGTUPLE 52 <dd:d> O
TAGTUPLE 178 Doctor I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 3 Wallace I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 Olympias I-PER
TAGTUPLE 338 text O
TAGTUPLE 6 Norton I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 25 Godfather I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 20 fat O
TAGTUPLE 53 ecclesiastical O
TAGTUPLE 3 Manned I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 7 naturalists O
TAGTUPLE 6 Globemaster I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 15 Silver I-PER
TAGTUPLE 7 alleges O
TAGTUPLE 57 monarch O
TAGTUPLE 9 honorable O
TAGTUPLE 5 navel O
TAGTUPLE 8 Kaika I-PER
TAGTUPLE 8 fences O
TAGTUPLE 112 Common I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 50 Douglass I-PER
TAGTUPLE 4 Moran I-PER
TAGTUPLE 103 legacy O
TAGTUPLE 18 cope O
TAGTUPLE 1103 place O
TAGTUPLE 7 Yerevan I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 2 See I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 Anniversary I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 18 chipsets O
TAGTUPLE 15 thematic O
TAGTUPLE 6 semi-autobiographical O
TAGTUPLE 97 bottom O
TAGTUPLE 12 Valley I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 12 Weyl I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 policy I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 73 threw O
TAGTUPLE 1 Tong I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Regions I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 Euratom I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 docking I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 10 Baudot I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 Amazon I-PER
TAGTUPLE 9 Reich I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 59 navy O
TAGTUPLE 10 rewrite O
TAGTUPLE 24 spreading O
TAGTUPLE 50 walk O
TAGTUPLE 26 obstacle O
TAGTUPLE 4 Reed I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 upholding O
TAGTUPLE 10 exhibiting O
TAGTUPLE 2 Jews I-PER
TAGTUPLE 5 highlands I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 10 <xddd> O
TAGTUPLE 44 motorcycle O
TAGTUPLE 25 Weber I-PER
TAGTUPLE 22 congregation O
TAGTUPLE 1 360 I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 85 Romania I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 recognition I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 50 assume O
TAGTUPLE 20 invisible O
TAGTUPLE 11 Nord I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 8 Troy I-PER
TAGTUPLE 4 Korean I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 11 digit O
TAGTUPLE 14 conditional O
TAGTUPLE 3 Bridges I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 54 doctors O
TAGTUPLE 13 militants O
TAGTUPLE 9 Key I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 publication I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 Tornado I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 updated I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Slavic I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 147 1950 O
TAGTUPLE 402 18 O
TAGTUPLE 9 joystick O
TAGTUPLE 43608 <xxxx> O
TAGTUPLE 20 peacefully O
TAGTUPLE 24 Land I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 S. I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 79 43 O
TAGTUPLE 5 archers O
TAGTUPLE 191 roles O
TAGTUPLE 1 men I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 76 Belarus I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 6 crystalline O
TAGTUPLE 6 Freddy I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 solidus O
TAGTUPLE 14 Cryonics I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 2 Screw I-PER
TAGTUPLE 7 Methodius I-PER
TAGTUPLE 9 candle O
TAGTUPLE 1 Communications I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 3 Taunus I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 3 <XxXx> I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 24 Oman I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 7 Nothing I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Acre I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 806 August O
TAGTUPLE 12 Ghana I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 51 interpreter O
TAGTUPLE 18 Ampère I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Lewis O
TAGTUPLE 21 passionate O
TAGTUPLE 11 duplicated O
TAGTUPLE 12 attendees O
TAGTUPLE 21 extraction O
TAGTUPLE 25 1541 O
TAGTUPLE 6 pathology O
TAGTUPLE 5 clumps O
TAGTUPLE 10 AFL I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 Thirteen I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 8 1:1 O
TAGTUPLE 37 Faraday I-PER
TAGTUPLE 4 Cartier I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 7 fellows O
TAGTUPLE 105 weather O
TAGTUPLE 29 Buenos I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 3 Chang I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 12 tackle O
TAGTUPLE 1 Jamestown I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 5 Molière I-PER
TAGTUPLE 6 Oulu I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 14 Velázquez I-PER
TAGTUPLE 21 photo O
TAGTUPLE 129 <Xx-xx> I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 57 shorter O
TAGTUPLE 1 Mad I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 Guns I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 4 Sunset I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 9 Newcomb I-PER
TAGTUPLE 10 Sonny I-PER
TAGTUPLE 14 well-established O
TAGTUPLE 67 interactive O
TAGTUPLE 72 Jerry I-PER
TAGTUPLE 13 undermine O
TAGTUPLE 6 155 O
TAGTUPLE 11 Tezuka I-PER
TAGTUPLE 116 ranks O
TAGTUPLE 1 Charlottetown I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 adrenaline O
TAGTUPLE 29 pursuing O
TAGTUPLE 77 People I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 Rob I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 1 professor I-PER
TAGTUPLE 10 Abbahu I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Bernard I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 111 actress O
TAGTUPLE 5 monotonous O
TAGTUPLE 1 Racing I-PER
TAGTUPLE 26 graffiti O
TAGTUPLE 2 Borough I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 39.4 O
TAGTUPLE 17 Minister I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 31 King I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 1 Arrow I-PER
TAGTUPLE 1 Childe I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 3 β I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 19 bullpen O
TAGTUPLE 11 Herald I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 5 octave O
TAGTUPLE 15 dolphins O
TAGTUPLE 1 Groningen I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 21 Atchison I-PER
TAGTUPLE 139 Black I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 1 rising I-ORG
TAGTUPLE 4 1911 I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 3 Howe I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 10 civilization I-LOC
TAGTUPLE 18 remark O
TAGTUPLE 71 circuit O
TAGTUPLE 1 Clearwater I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 2 Array I-MISC
TAGTUPLE 7 Internal O
TAGTUPLE 7 exhumed O
TAGTUPLE 1 Former I-MISC
